Conditioned this day and age a friendly face on every page
a laugh track floating through the haze
Everything feels safe these days
The neighbors wave the children play
The sunshine's bright the bills get paid a perfect house
a perfect street a
Perfect smile perfect beat my day, but
Someone brought me a joint last night, that was nice.
I'm still piecing together exactly what happened.
Still pretty confused.
I think I'm getting a better idea of what the mindset is now.
But she's wrong.
I mean, that whole thing is like...
I saw...
I was watching that day.
I saw what was happening.
Was it something I could intervene in?
Maybe?
I mean, maybe a kid up here.
Here's the thing.
I was watching that day about Karl Foll and Mimi
in that situation.
I was watching that episode.
I was commenting.
I was just watching.
And then I saw someone say Brandon's going off
on his own chat or in his chat about Alex and stuff.
And so I went over there and he was on the phone
with the INX and I was like, okay,
well, if anyone knows how to talk to him,
Probably took a nap or something that day. I know I did a couple lives
I was I talked to them before anything happened at both of them. I was like, you know, you should you know, just
try carefully on you know going off on on her and
The next thing I know I'm a being called like a drug dealer or something
Like sitting sitting meth
Through to other streamers or something like that. I don't know. I'm gonna get meth gang
We we pretend we're PDFs in order to
Get the attention away from the our meth dealings or something. I mean, that's a little far-fetched. I'm not a little
I mean a lot. I mean it's like and then
Well now it's like now we're trying to protect Carl
don't think any of us any of any of the three like the three of us like him at
all like I don't think he was about trying to distract away from your topic
and I am sorry if I was it because I streamed at the same time because I was
ending my lives like sending people to ears like when I found out you were
streaming Alex I mean I tried my best I don't know but now I guess I'm the bad
Handler he doesn't need I mean he's like you know I don't think he needs to handle it, but I'm not his I
Don't know. I'm not somebody that he probably would listen to about things. I don't I don't know I
Just I don't know how it's like my fault. Everything's my fault now
I I I tried to still be nice to everybody. I mean, I don't know
Oftentimes I get blamed for things
It's not like me complaining. It's not me saying anything about it. It's just me saying
This just happened the second she didn't she understand I go play for so I just understand like
What happened? I mean, it's like really I didn't do like maybe maybe the point was I didn't do anything
I should have like been all up in everybody's
conversations and
Getting involved and I just maybe I
I'm slower to do that sometimes
But if I did something wrong, I'm sorry. I mean it's like but again, there's only so much I can do
Oh God, anyway, I have some good fish tacos that I need to put in this whole bag, so this is a
beautiful Russian woman
Brought me some last day. I did a reading for her here. It's my third time. She's come over
for reading and so I mean I didn't do no
I've never charged her, I just think, you know, she's always said,
oh, do you want me to bring you something,
or do you want to eat or something like that?
And then she's brought me like stuff and I do it really.
And it's like, it's like, I thought,
so I'm not like a extortionist.
I'm not like a, I'm so, I don't know.
I'm as ethical and fair as I could possibly be.
All right, I don't know.
I don't know, but I mean, I think I'd have to.
I don't know because there's always something you can say about people that do
You know things in the east of terror for metaphysical fields
You can always do people. Some people think they're all phonies and people think they're all real and people think
Different things. I don't think it's entertainment. Some people think it's you know, um, uh,
I
It's just like there's so much
But I I'm a decent I'm a decent um pair reader
You know, maybe there's better ones. Maybe there's another the worst ones. I know I'm not the worst, so
But you know, you should live better ones, too
Anyway, I don't I don't even push it on people. I don't push it on people. I don't
Hi, babe. Hi. Hi
Jimmy oh week me. Oh, hi babe. Hi rude
So, I don't know. I'm just I guess I was just getting my thoughts out. Hi. Oh, there's Brandon. Hey, what's up, Brandon?
And now, I mean, I just don't, I don't really like how kind of like all three of us got turned on at once and it's like now we're being blamed for whatever it is.
I don't know, like what are we being blamed for?
For trying to defend Carl.
I mean of all things, Carl, I mean I can't stand Carl.
I was cheering on Summer with the Mimi thing.
I was sending Alex the message they got from Mimi and stuff.
I mean, I was trying to help as much as I could.
With her story and I wasn't even covering her. I mean I was saying and so I was like, I don't know
I don't know. Maybe I stepped on her toes somehow. I don't quite understand though, but it happens. It happens. Okay
so
Yeah, I'm sorry. Oh, I mean, it's like, you know, I maybe will figure us more. I mean, it's like the thing is I would have liked
At least talked you kind of conversation instead of just like hi Brandon
Can't hear you
Might have to come yeah come back come on right back up. Um, I don't know I mean it's like we
One second. We're all friends
There's like a little fracture in it, but I think there's still friendships that were maintained
Maybe they're made a little bit more separate and this like you know good, but um
Well now it's just a big man. I mean now it's like, you know
Now we're the enemies. She's now. She's friends with crystal again. Oh
Friends with gamble again, right? Hey, Brandon
I don't know what's wrong with your mic.
I mean, is it me?
Maybe, is anyone hearing him?
I don't hear him.
Is my stuff off, or do you guys hear me?
I don't know.
I do like your avatar, if you can hear me.
It reminds me of something called the Umbrella Network.
Swiss army, it's a divine intervention. You think so are two. Oh, it's just sad
It's like now. I mean, I'll get called out that we've been called what I'm being called extortionist
Like oh, I'm a fakes like again. We're fakes like okay, so here we go
brain him
Hey, there we go. I don't know what that was going on my son, man
Are you good good? Good morning, bro. Is he going?
It's okay. Good morning. I mean, I was watching this like thing yesterday and said, oh, here's the here's a truth about
Extortionists, you know, yeah with my name out and I know that I know she's saying oh, you'll be arrest
Oh, you know stuff about oh you're something was gonna happen to you
She says something's gonna happen to me
She says something that someone's gonna have to step in and do something. Oh, yeah
And then me too in six days something that I would never expect that
Nobody's had the courage to do is gonna happen in six days also
I mean, what is that a threat?
What is that?
That's not like a threat saying, oh, something he wouldn't expect
and nobody has the courage to do.
Like, what the fuck does that mean?
Like, I don't know.
And she's supposedly by my house, too, allegedly.
Right. I mean, she says she's in like, you know, I mean, I don't I don't think she's really there
But I mean maybe she is she was giving me her her exact location. Oh, yeah
She's posting that address like for what like she's nuts. Oh, yeah. Oh, and you didn't you didn't hear man
I went all the way to clumsy dude and forced him to delete that live on Carl to protect Carl
Yeah, I mean it's like what yeah, I mean these things are like I mean it's like the ideas that she get
I mean it's like it seems like some kind of like paranoia
It's like skits a friend. Yeah, like skit-soid
Because I yeah, I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. It just seems like it's like we're fine that day
She's having a tripod the next thing I know
party gifts and then I think now I've like and she's either I never asked her for
Anything I never I never asked her she would
Sometimes surprise me with things and that's always fun to have a friend that does that right, but it's not like
that's not the only reason I was friends with her or anything like that.
It was like, you know, just literally, we were talking the phone for hours,
like probably every week, you know, at least once or twice a week, we would, you know,
talk for several hours on the phone. We had, we always had good conversations. Like when things
are good, they're very good. And when things go bad, they just go, it goes like so opposite,
She'll be friends with me and Carl. I mean, it's like what's gonna happen. I don't understand. It's like to
It's too much like a change in the brain is they is a musical chairs or you know, I don't know
It's borderline personality and schizophrenic
It's like and then it's like old prison you go. I'm gonna get killed. I'm going to prison and all you're going to prison like it's nuts
We were like we're not we haven't been charged
I mean like what is this and now is it what so now desperately trying to like get back charges of her for what for like internet clips
I mean, it's like she saw she's seen all this information too. And it's like and then all of a sudden she's like, oh, well
Oh, I didn't know about this and well, it's been months. I mean
Sitting for anything to try to convince. I mean, it's like she's seen everything. She's seen everything
Oh, yeah, and then saying go all gamble. Have you gone to the cops?
And then Ganville admits that I've done nothing wrong.
He says that the detectives in Albuqueria,
he's all they suck, they're nasty.
He's all they told me if there's no victim,
they can't do anything.
So what does that tell you?
If there's no victim, there's no crime.
So he's admitting it.
Right. I mean, he's like, oh, well, you know, you know, they had someone has to press charges or something like that.
Yeah, see I have to do something. Yeah, I mean, it's what I'm sure somebody if you did something
Well, there'd be charges to press but there's not like I mean, yeah, there'd be a victim there'd be a victim
They say okay, you molested this kid you did that you did that
Nothing there's nothing they could do
There's no crime. There's no victim. If the cops are saying that there's no victim that has to be a victim
They're telling you that he has to do something to somebody right to go to jail
That they're gonna general. Oh, well, you know, it's like, oh, he's just he's a pedophile walk him up. Oh fuck
I mean, that's how she said, oh, well, they're like none of them are actually pedophiles. They're but they but they
Like they say that so people will not look at their drug dealing online. Yeah, which is what's what's worse?
You get in more trouble for her pedo for a kid. She had been drugs. Right. Yeah
But you know, I don't know I
I'm trying to like I maybe we'll take it more is like
I didn't ask her once I was like how much of your personality is
Genuine about like what you're saying and how much of it. Yeah control
I think she told me she's like about 25 percent of what she does this troll and then like a 75 percent is like
Completely so I think I keep getting like stuck in this troll side of her personality and stuff and it's like because
I didn't like I really didn't do anything and that day it was like had nothing to do with me
She was she's not just saying oh, we're trying to
stuff. I saw people from talking about Carl and Mimi and stuff. Yeah. I I I I never did
that. I mean it was like I don't even know who that dude is. I don't even know who he
is. And now it's like they're saying oh he was a mod for Gamble or Gamble. I mean it's
getting so straight. It's like straight. It's just straight and it's like I can't keep up
with it really like. And a lot of its intimidation a lot of it is is just to oh.
She thinks that I'm gonna be scared. Oh, no, she's gonna give me put in jail for what? I haven't done anything wrong, dude
That's not gonna work empty
Same thing everybody does the same thing gamble and all his little buddies his little Australian buddy
They would always do that. They'd be like, hey, if you don't stop this
Oh in six days in three days, this is gonna all this is gonna happen. Nothing ever happens, bro
Right. It's always in three days. I'm going to jail in three days. I'm gonna lose my channel in three days
Uh, I'm going to get all the empty thrits.
It was really weird.
Like one time, you know, she was doing these memes of me and stuff.
And like nerves, like the police in the background, like outside my house.
And like during that time, the police came like almost every day.
I was and so it, but it was probably me manifesting or something.
You know, it was it was not probably nothing to do with her, but it's like there's power in like putting ideas of people's heads
Sometimes they don't manifest because they'll either like, you know focus on them thinking about them or believe me Nancy
How are you? But yeah, Texas roads? Yeah, I agree. Yeah, I think that
You know
But I don't know why it's like what the benefit is. I don't know if it's just content for her
I mean, it's just I don't know. I don't know it's hate. She's a hateful person man. Like she just gets mad and
Right and then she'll get well the thing is is like these people are doing shit
That they should expect somebody to get mad at and then their response is like
Oh, you're going to prison like god damn me. Yeah, it is a little blame-shifting because it's like and then it's like
I like like saying that I'm somehow responsible for for your behavior and I'm supposed
Mad at you for being mad at being mad at you for me
I have the right bro if somebody's acting like they're my friends saying oh this person my true friend and then they go
Talking to somebody that's an enemy of me. I have that right. I'm not wrong. I have that right bro like
And be like hey, I don't like you anymore. Bye. I have that right, bro
And I wasn't like I like went and like was like Alex you think a brandon take a Brandon's cause and stuff like that
I mean, yeah
She was listening to you and then she decided on her own. She wanted to get involved and there
That's her her hat in the ring or wherever she got herself involved because she saw the view the drama and shit that you were getting
So she wanted to get involved. She's like, oh my god. Look
Yeah, that's all it is and I mean I mean I mean and then you know all then she's like oh
I want Brandon John to come on. Oh so Brandon
And you know
Yeah, I want them to come on the show and like talk and stuff like that
So I got even more kind of put in like in the middle of things in that situation and stuff
Yeah, and then so it's like then but then to say that oh, I'm
I've set her up or something like that.
This doesn't make sense to me, and it's kind of upsetting.
But I mean, it's like, you know, again, it's like, you know,
really, at the end of the day, I know,
like, did I know this was going to happen?
Like, something or other, she'd be mad about.
I can't, I mean, it's like, I don't know.
It's like, it's like, for a few months.
Yeah, what's up, dude? How are you?
You know what's up, dude?
Look at my cat. Look, my cat hates me, by the way. Look.
Yeah.
He begs for me as soon as I get home. Look at him.
Look at what he does.
That's a Siamese cat. He's a beautiful cat. Yeah.
See how he like rolls over? He'll roll like that on the carpet
and then drag himself with his paws towards me.
Yeah.
Like he'll be laying down like that and he uses his front paws
and drags his body towards me while laying like this.
And I know I know your cat loves you and my cats love me. I mean it's like I mean that this is not people say
Oh, like my cats hate me because my cat hissed or like one of my cats. Yeah
Yeah, but
No, that's what they're saying too about me that oh your cat hates you his cat hates him. He hates his cat hates him
Yeah, like literally I literally the north's like on me and then like, you know behind me is like there's low love
You're always if they they're always like next to me like they they just think they're
Let me oh, that's a cute cat. Yeah, so I mean I could get him I could get him to bite me though
Yeah, I mean it's like but that's we cats cats are playful like that's what they do. Yeah, that's what they do
They like if you if you think you know you can get their belly like but it's the and they see I know like Lord doesn't bite me or like
You know or she wouldn't like our scratch or another with Lola
But you know that the cat tux that came in is he was been he's been like outs
I mean outside for like a year and a half or like, you know more of on a street cat feral bases and then he's so he's a little bit
more wild, but he still like was like, you know, started to like come in and then started slowly like, you know, walking over my lap and then, you know, like sitting next to me and stuff like that.
So it's like, you know, I just, with cats, you don't push, you let them come to you. Basically, that's what my, it's like, I like, that's why cats like sometimes they like people that don't like cats because the person will like be ignoring the cat and like not making eye contact.
Being like a little bit ignored or like not paid attention to in a certain way because then they don't feel threatened by certain people, but
Yeah, exactly. Yeah, they don't like when you try to chase them
Yeah, have you heard of
Parasol because I'm thinking your avatars. There's no parasol. I think or like
It's a mom resonant evil. That's the umbrella logo. Yeah, the umbrella and I said the umbrella
Like that but that's actually in Switzerland
You see I was red and white and there actually is like a secret society Switzerland has eight. It's called octagon a what?
Yeah, octagon. Yeah, and it has
See also you can see like the night's Templar cross comes out in the middle of that, right?
But it's also like an umbrella. It's like, you know, which is like if you look under umbrella
It's like segmented like that. So yeah, that's probably where they got it from. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, cuz it's like the it's like a corporation like they're supposedly like a pharmaceutical, but
Yeah, behind the scenes. They make like fucking bio weapons and shit
Eight branches of it like an octopus so it's called octogon or something like that and yeah
There's a guy there's a guy actually
That goes into switzerland with his camera
And he's been arrested there a bunch of times and he goes around and he goes around he goes around to these
These Rothschild mansions. He goes. Yeah
To night's Templar churches and stuff like that where he gets to get out of them and stuff
And I mean, yeah, you might want to look like look up octagon, Switzerland
Guy does really good videos, but yeah, check it out. He taught me a lot of umbrella stuff. I might play that later. Yeah
But anyway, so how's your weekend? It's like
Yeah, everything's pretty good. I went to the grocery store now, you know, you know
I an act she's been going and running a gamble and shit and then but I don't even care dude
Like if she wants to do that, that's on her. You know what I mean?
She's the one that loses a friend bro. So that's all on her dude
And I have the right to hey, I don't want to deal with this
But then it's like I think like people take advantage of that to like, you know, kind of like
Yeah, it's not a win like crystal things that me cutting her off is like a win
How is that a win? That's not a win when I cut somebody off and then she takes her in with open arms
Even Sam Man went on her panel last night and was clowning on her for that's like bro
Karen I and X swatted her calls her family all this and that but look look willing to tape
Oh eating her own vomit Sam Man was saying and it's true
They're eating their own eating their own shit and bomb it bro. Just because I got mad at her like that. That's crazy, dude
Well, yeah, I mean, it's like, yeah, I mean, like, you know, you know, we know you have like a temper sometimes
But it's like, you know, there's nothing like that can't be
You are like a reasonable person and like, you know, sometimes people sometimes will react and then they'll calm down a little bit
I like to talk to people when like that wouldn't like that the emotions that come down a little bit
That it's easier to like I'm telling you
Like a when it's not not emotional all emotions involved with it's a little easier to discuss. Yeah
But, I mean, I don't know, I think that people are trying to try to like run to everybody that
like say, oh, well, you're not putting them anymore, let's be friends, let's hate Bond over this.
I mean, they'll say, but like literally Crystal like ran to Alex like last night and then Alex is so happy to like
Literally like three days ago there that she's like, oh, they ever talk to me again
Like you know this person trying to kill me like blah blah blah blah. See I never did any of these things like these threats
And so it's like for that for her like so be like just run run over and be their friend and then
It doesn't make sense logically it doesn't none of it makes sense dude. It's just like
Like, you know, I wrote her a message and she looked at me back and she's like,
I was like, well, what did I do? I said, all I did was I love you and be nice.
And she's like, you know exactly what you did.
Again, I hate that because it's like what did I do? Yeah, it's yeah, that's bullshit. That's gas lighting cuz it's like
Then tell me then tell me what I did. You know what you did
Yeah, I know I know what I did it's like I know what you did last summer kind of thing
It's like well, yeah, I did a lot of terrible things last summer like which one I mean is that yeah
And then we're gonna start bidding every bad day and then I say oh, I didn't know you did all that
But I was mad about this, you know, yeah, it's a lazy script. It's a lazy excuse. You know what I mean?
She could say you didn't do this. You didn't stand up for me here
But she can't yeah, cuz she can't say none of that so that's why she said that cuz she can't say anything
You know what you did
Because there's no discussion before and nothing and then even she was like
We have a guest coming on okay, maybe this will clear some things up who is it?
Hey, psyche that bitch is going crazy. I thought that what she said to Brandon and she's fucking with me
She's insane. I mean, I'm sick of the back and forth Alex
I'm sick of this, you know, and just because Barb went at her
I appreciated Bob for going at her on crystals live. I was surprised because she has issues with her
So, you know, I'm glad Barb was there. So I went up
And she doesn't want shit to do with her and she's batshit crazy and she's lying and she's packing Rick. She I've I don't follow
Zaya she's obsessed with him psyche
She's the one that was there watching telling me that she got a membership and something about Sue
That was in there and she wanted to clip that and ask me if I watch it and I said no don't watch him
And she said well, I got the membership and then she got upset because they cut that video short
I guess because she joined and they won her taking it or maybe that and she was a member for a while
And then she went up there to kiss her ass after what she did to them and she does this with every one of us
She goes back and forth takes you do the same thing
Brandon I went in there because I'm sick of the shit that she's doing and that's why I went in because look at what she's posted
She's saying that I wanted her to make a long video of Crystal remember
Didn't she tell you too because she told me and I have proof of that that she had a long version and she was gonna post it
That's what she said it. I think you know you went on with me, but yeah, it's just bullshit
You're talking about all those people. How is that a bot that's specifically going back responding to everything?
If you look at that live, they said it's bot and they that's why they don't answer
They're full of shit dude. It's lazy run
There's multiple people in my community bro that are in Q army and and gamble on them
They're scared of him because they fucking it
Yeah, just stop getting so mad you get so violent threatening when you do that
No, I mean the way your text first you apologize for yesterday and then yeah, I didn't know yeah
And then I look and saw that you that you're over there fucking kissing gambles ass gamble. It's good good bro gamble
Literally showed his ass to a little kid. That's unacceptable. Mm-hmm. Yeah, I don't know what's going on
But the bitch is going too far, you know, and and she's involving them or whatever
So if he wants to be cool, why doesn't he tell her hey chill cuz he knows all about her
Right because you know or so they're so happy like that it's like she's come to their side kind of
Yeah, and they fall for it when they all agreed. She's a psycho
I mean look at Tommy when she was so desperate for him calling her her boyfriend
And he was already bashing her on the live that I clip I still have it
Like it's gonna hurt me they act they feel like that's gonna like that's winning against me
But no, she's eating her own vomit. That's all you're doing
Just like Santa said eating your own vomit eating your own eating your own shit and vomit bro isn't hurting me
Yeah, and then that's what she's doing too with everybody, but you're right
It's just this stupid, but I just liked what Barb had to say because now she's bashing Barb
And she's tagging Rick when yes Rick did dox her to us a long time ago when he was at war with her
She knows that
And she's trying to say, I said it, I said it, bitch, that's not true.
I have the proof of everything.
I keep all those texts, you know, and he had an issue with her
because he had Tommy on his live talking about her having AIDS
and how she was paranoid and walked fast when she'd get out of the car
and go to the store looking around because I guess people are after her
because all this shit she's done.
Yeah
Left chicken Andy string. He was there for five minutes and he bounced
Chicken Andy. I don't know. I don't watch chicken Andy. I didn't even know he was watching either. I don't watch it either
Somebody just told me yeah
Like like I don't watch they and she was in there kissing his ass and they were laughing at her and he was rolling his eyes
And then a tune and she left they laughed and bastard and called her hawk-eyed
Oh, yeah
Psyche, you know how gambles always ain't no Brandon's gotten so fat and all this and that he went and stream sniped chicken Andy on his little
jet ski and
Bro, oh my god. Did you see a clear view of him from like somebody else's camera his whole body?
Bro, he is literally a little short fat midget bro blow dude who?
Get no gamble. I didn't say chicken Andy. I'm when I was seeing that
I was showing it last night. I was showing gamble on video him on his jet ski
And then I'm like he's not even half as long as his jet ski and then they're he coming in on chats on his
Oaks to defend him. He's like well the jet. He's 11 feet long
I'm like, oh wow, so what oh, he's not even half half as long as 11 feet
So that makes him what five feet tall. Oh my whoa
I mean, I don't right now it's gonna be kind of a dangerous time because there are the all the people are gonna try to like
Like certain that there are other people to annoy people and you know how
Situations and so it's like, you know, just like beware of like and my homie. Yeah, and my homie was on the boat
So they were on a boat chicken Andy and some other dude in my homie
We're on a boat in Miami in the same area where he showed his asshole to the little boy in the same area in the water
And uh, so, uh, Ganville pulls up on his jet ski with a knife, dude.
He had a knife on his leg.
It looked gayer than hell, bro.
It looked like, you know how chicks carry like a knife or a gun under their
pantyhose?
Yeah.
Like it was like that.
Like it was like that around his fat little short leg, dude.
And he pulled up and first thing he gets with the first thing he starts talking about.
Me.
He starts talking about me saying and then he tells my home. He's all what's so crispy
He's also are you gonna denounce Brandon? Are you gonna call him a pedophile?
He's like no, he's like no, he's I'm not gonna say that and then gamble just left you went and left dude after like five minutes, dude
I don't know what other
Right, but right now it's like being it's like it's like a puzzle cards because it's like I mean it's like it's not really
Like there's nothing in foundation
Through what she's saying about that's like like that. Yeah. Yeah, that's ring like where's the money then?
Why where's your all your money then if you're a mess dealer, I don't know
Where's all your money like it makes no sense
Right, I mean, it's like
There is like, you know, I mean it does turn into like oh, I don't know how bad this one will get but it's like last time
I turn into like there's I just need to like I'm just trying to be nice
And I'm not gonna like fight her and like you know like last time I was fighting good
I'm not gonna fight it and stuff. I'm not gonna bother her or whatever
I did text her a couple times because it's not I don't like just like
all of a sudden being accused of all this stuff and I dropped and like you know and then not even
having done anything like there's nothing in it I did like I mean maybe that was it that I didn't
go because you didn't do anything yeah I didn't I didn't go go soothe you or something that day
because she was like she was like oh can someone she said put someone go over tell Brandon to like
calm down or something like that and I and then I went I like went to your chat and then you're
is probably the best person to talk to him or calm him down.
Yeah.
But, um, and so the next thing I know, it's like, I'm turning,
I'm turning on against and it's like, and then as for Carl and Mimi,
like I have no, no, a horse in that race or whatever.
I mean, it's like, I don't like Carl.
I feel like Mimi was, you know, being, being used or being like, uh,
Like fishing around for something in the community and stuff, you know
Okay, well, it's a gamble so gambles autistic. I mean, it's like, okay, you know, that's what is that?
That is so that makes it okay to show your ass to a little boy
That makes it okay to groom kids and get them arrested by the FBI
That makes it okay to be a 29 year old man raking a 16 year old girl because autism by the way
Well, I think I think I mean it's like we can say
Autism or something on the spectrum for almost like everybody around here. Sometimes everybody's autistic now
Yeah, I don't know. It's like you mean it's like we as
Things I'm not a psychiatrist. I'm not a
You know, a police officer and it is I can't really make this I might really even involved in most of the situations and stuff like that
Why is the guy talking about weird stuff?
Because we're talking about gamble cuz gambles are weirdo and a pedophile and we're talking and I'm talking about gamble
The pedophile that lives with his dad in North Miami that is on video showing his ass to a little boy
I mean, yeah, I mean it's like yeah, I mean there's weird behavior. That's what they always say
That's what they come in our notes and then when you start exposing them. They'll be like here. Why is he so you're talking about weird stuff?
Why are you always talking about kids?
Okay, like to like get me to stop. No, that's what the fuck
Sorry about that it fell out because I had to answer a call
Yeah, I don't know. This is also crazy though, but especially that big turn of instigate and all you know just I mean
It's bad. She's insane. There's so much out there about her. She's on the run because she's got one and
Tommy was telling the truth. Nope. Not about AIDS. I don't believe that. I don't know where that came from
But about the other stuff because he said it with her when they were both live together and he was saying and she was saying he's my boyfriend now and she was so happy.
And he said when make something clear that she does mail down there or whatever I have that clip but I never posted it.
and she was sitting there like shaking her head.
She was just desperate to have them.
It's weird because she's the lonely one
that can't even have a man.
And she was so mad and crying when Zaya and Peb got
a hold of him and he told them the truth about her,
how he didn't want a relationship with her
and she was too stockish or something.
And he was done with her because she was going on
about him being, this guy being her boyfriend.
No, they had sex once or whatever and and then she started stalking him and that's disgusting
Yeah, they have that and that guy Dutchie was there
Then that's the guy she was saying. He's good looking and kicks him
I mean she just goes back and forth. I she's got serious mental issues
Disgusting, you know and yeah, I mean I was thinking about what she said about Zea when she was in there trying to record
She did record the video, but I had nothing to do with it
I don't follow him and she's trying to say that I told her get the video or something
It's like I don't know what goes on in there. She's the one that stalks them
I don't watch zea and they got so many channels. I wouldn't even know which channel they're on
Yeah, and then she made the ai on peb 2 and she made the one on crystal
Yeah, you know she made the one on crystal and she told us she made to had a long version. She was gonna post
I mean, you know, I did she's the one doing this shit and
And she does this to everybody and so many take her back like I did and she's just she needs help
You know, I mean, she doesn't get along with her own mom and her sister because she was naked and dancing
They said they even sent the clip that was when she was threatening Donnie
They sent me that clip of her pulling that knife and threatened to cut her or something on the live and she was drunk
you know that was from a few years ago I'd say it's insane that she does this
and her whole channel is trapped and she's crazy and she's reporting us for
it because she can't stand the truth or our reaction
Well, she's ready to kill me. She's ready to do something. She says that in six days something that I would never expect is gonna happen
Yeah, she says that to people like me too
Who's harassing her she's harassing everybody by making these weird videos and and
Wiki info when she contacted my brother a year ago, and I didn't know that and when I went to ICU because I got sick
And then I ended up in, you know, the rehab, the physical rehab to learn to walk again because
I was like dying, you know, that's what they said, they had me and I see you for a week.
And when I was talking to them then, he said, I was a person of wiki info, whatever, a woman
says you're best friends with Larry, the math head.
And I said, who's Larry?
And I said, the wiki info called in, and you're doing math, is that how you had lost all that
You know as yeah, it's just crazy and and so I was in the facility and I didn't want to deal with that and I blocked them
And then I worked on myself to get better because they said I'd be there a long time
And I, you know, because I wanted to get out of there and talk to them, you know, it's, it was horrible.
And as soon as I was discharged on the first Friday of September last year, I went straight to their house the next morning, you know, and to talk to them about it.
And they looked at me and they were relieved.
And I said, look at me. Do I look like I do meth?
I said, you would know what a meth head looks like.
And then he smiled and he was happy and he's that was kidding no
He wasn't he really did think that because he was screaming at me when on that call when I was in that facility
He's just dangerous. He's a piece of shit. She's crazy and everybody sees that and they go along with her
But yeah, there's a big a streamer that she's scared of that what was co-hosting
So she showed a lot on her and her own receipts and her experience with her and some last live that she joined with them
Where she was humiliated by that person
Yeah, and and and her ex-friend who I communicate with sometimes even told me about it because she's close to that person and I that's how that person reached out to me we talked.
One time we talked on the phone so she shared that stuff and that's the person that's doing a deep dive on her but she needs to shut up.
She's crazy and it's sad because she's a beautiful lady and she's so intelligent and she's got a great personality but she has anger in the way she.
Goes at people with lies and stuff. Why?
Delusional schizophrenic delusional. Yes, that's what that person said that streamer on that live and she co-hosted it
She wouldn't her own live, but she co-hosted it with one of the bigger streamer
And you know and she said that she's schizophrenic, and I guess that's what it is
I don't know anything about, you know that
It was like seems like it was like three months where it was like negative never negative experience and then all
And one day it turns into like everything is negative.
I mean, everything has gotten negative.
And now we go into the drug trafficker.
Yeah, drug trafficking or we're meth heads.
And, you know, it's just insane, you know?
It's crazy.
Yeah, but damn because I was like if it was like you know day by day like day to day
Changes and stuff like that. That would make sense or like a skit's a free or like a bipolar
but because it was like three months of like
Not none of that and then all of a sudden it's her
And you know what, she even thanked me for the, she even said it on, on one of her videos
that she thanked me for having that convo with her dad.
And I have his text because he even thanked me for the conversation.
I have the text.
He wanted me to talk to him because somebody sent us to him because they were fucking with them.
And I, and I took the number and, and texted, you know, hey, chill out, calm down.
And they said, well, you sound different than this other person or whatever.
Some man, he was talking about that streamer.
And then he said can you call me and I did and we had a great combo he was a good man he loves his daughter and he adores Alex he said she was her favorite.
And say that a lot of nice things about he was a really nice man because he was even concerned about the person.
And to tell this person about the MD Anderson hospital out here that it's the best in in the states or in the world
I don't know, but it's one of the best and I told them I said
They're not here. They're in Michigan
He he was concerned and he said well, I wish him the best and you know, it was that he was a really nice man
And he's the one that asked me to call him. I have that text. I saved it
And then I have the text that after that call it was only one call
After that call he thanked me for the time and I didn't realize he texted me after that
I found it a few months ago. It's like wait a minute who's that and I thought oh man
That's that's her dad, but you know what you know, this is stupid. Yes
We've all done some shit in the past calls and stuff
that's over with why continue and why is she doing this to everybody yeah and she's over here saying
that i want clumsy son like what the fuck oh and you know what and when i posted that post when i
posted that post of his facebook with a picture of him and his son guess who reshared that she did
she did i saw that she did and then she went and deleted it before saying that
Oh my God, see, that's how shady she is.
Yeah, like I could be dirty.
I could talk about her.
Dad, I could say all kinds of shit.
Look, have I said that?
All I said is that she's a backstabber and she's fake.
And she's over here saying that I'm going to prison that she's gonna get me arrested
No, she has a warrant out to go to New Jersey court
Yeah, I can go see his video about her with her
Criminal of stuff that where she's facing and and Amber was on there talking about it
There is an active warrant out for her and I'm not sure in Arizona. I don't care where it's that I wouldn't call on her
But they're they they're saying that if you call them let them that they said that they to let them know when she's there
Oh, really? So they're looking for her?
Yes, it's a communication harassment like the one I had and dealt with in court.
It's not, if it shows there's a warrant out, because what they told me here,
that's why I went to the court and turned myself in there, because I didn't want to take a chance of being pulled over,
driving, because they didn't tell me, they said, no, they're not going to come to your home or job.
But if you get pulled over and you give them your ID, it depends on the officer.
They'll probably let you go, but you never know, they're able to take you in.
Well, what was the warrant out of?
The mine?
Yeah, mine was here in Houston. No, it came to I had to go to court here
Yeah, but who what state was
Somebody from from no, it was it. No, I guess here you can transfer to their state
So how are they gonna be looking for her in Arizona when she was in Houston?
Right. Yeah. So what I'm saying is a lot of charges. If you have someone if you harass somebody that's in Arizona
And you don't live there the warrants going to be out of Arizona not out of your state
Yeah, that's what they said. They said if she gets pulled over because it's there
So yeah, so she goes and tries to tell the cops shit about me. They're gonna say well, who are you?
I need your name and they're gonna ask for her idea and they'll be like, oh, you have a warrant for stalking. Wow
You're stalking this dude, and then you came all the way over here to Albuquerque
They're gonna be like, yeah, I'm here a fucking stock. Yeah, you know, it's just so sad because you know they'll arrest her
They'll arrest me. Oh, they'll literally ask me wrote the console we here. I know them. They'll call me and ask me people
Like hey, do you want us to arrest her? I'll be like, yeah, the rest your ass. Yeah
For the extradition. Yeah, that's not gonna be expensive to extradite somebody from Arizona from New Mexico to Arizona
Yeah, I heard that about ski math. They could extradite him to New Jersey where they have
some warrants, especially when he got arrested where he's at. But that didn't happen.
It puts you in jail and then you have a hearing and you see a judge and it's called the Puget of
I'm the law hearing and then they decided they're gonna actually buy you or not
Wow, I've never gotten in any trouble outside of here, Texas
Never
Nowhere else just here and and that was like twice in a long time ago. I was young
You know it was stupid and I was lucky because I could have had a drug charge and instead
They took that off because my parents put me in a drug treatment with the
Palmer drug abuse
Program a case that counselor that they knew of and they paid her to help and
She got me in there and she'd call me because I wanted to get out and I said I'm getting out
What was it that she would say that's that's that's the drugs talking. That's what she said. Yeah, that's the drugs talking
That's not you. It's like what are you talking about? I said I'm sober here. I want to get out
Yeah, and I was there like for 60 days
It was like a hotel. It was beautiful that place and it was right next to our house. It was in Kingwood
Yeah, they change the name, but all that happened there
I met other drug addicts and a few one was way older than us and when we got out of there
She we were getting high with her
Yeah rehabs don't work because none of them wanted to recover like it was like let's go
to a meeting let's go to a meeting and instead they were getting hot meetings and amy and
a meetings and rehab they don't work because all you're going to be is around other drug
addicts and then talking about drugs all fucking day that's why it doesn't work yeah one time
they took us to an NA meeting and all those people do is like
Share war stories like they're excited about their past and I remember the person that was running. Yeah, one of the meetings was saying hey
You're here to recover
Not go back to your drive because that's what brought you here
Cuz they say they talk about yeah, I remember when I did this it was a good feeling and stuff and they everybody be laughing
It's like why aren't you all talking about recovery?
Yeah, cuz it doesn't work. They're just just to make money. They don't work
And it's any meetings don't work either a meetings don't work either
Right and the person that was in charge of the she was one of the drug counselors or something at that rehab
me and her
One of her daughters became best friends and she was still out using she was the biggest drug dealer and drug addict and her mom knew it
Yeah, it was it was crazy and then here. She is running. She's like a psychotherapist at that place. I think she was
Yeah, I'm gonna hop off my headphones died
So I'm gonna hop I'll be back
Okay, well, okay. Yeah. Okay. Yeah, psyche. So I don't know what and she and she's saying that you're asking her for money
I mean, you don't go out there to tell what she's talking about. It's it's just insane
Yeah, then you called her yesterday and you only asked for money
Yeah, I texted her yesterday and I said I said my door's always open
I said I don't know what I did, but I did but I and then she said well
You know what you did or yourself ish and all you care about it yourself
That's it. It's just crazy that she gets like that
I don't know what she's been through in her past to be like that because like I said
You know, she I don't know. She's just um, I don't know. I don't get it
I don't either well, I don't see a brand in them boys or something like that or maybe that happens because I know someone that he's so smart very good looking.
He's got everything to and and you know he's successful all of that but he has a crazy temper on the side that not everybody sees I've seen that side of him not not with me.
And and it's scary it's like why do you get like that.
Right, I mean trauma response. I think like you know for having to defend yourself from so many crazy accusations, right?
Yeah, it's crazy and I don't I hate that I have to react and defend myself
When she could she could be reported and all and you lose everything like she did Twitter because they have all her stuff from Twitter
Wayne to hurt her
Unalive herself all of that and I don't need to be sent all that though
You know, there's just people that's like alright
You already posted it you had issues with her like the knife of her pulling it on some lady named Donnie
And so I go wow and then the wife of the Donnie guy that she talks about is the one
that sent some information, though, too, because she watches YouTube.
I didn't know who she was, you know, because she has more to say about her.
But it's just insane. She just needs to chill out.
She'll be up all night doing video after video, and she's stalking us all,
reacting, and she just wants to have wars between people.
And I respected Barb for standing up to her.
She's pissed at Barb because Barb doesn't want shit to do with her.
She sees right through her.
And Barb is friends with that guy that she's trying to tag, you know, she's very good friends with them
But I don't get it. You know, I people warn me do not give her chance when they saw her
You know glazing me and the first time she did it was through that Melissa when we got into it or whatever and
That Melissa messaged me on discord saying oh, she's saying that she wants to you're welcome in her chat
You can she wants to invite you to go to Olive Garden with her
And then when I went there a few days later, she's,
oh, I'm thinking shit after what you've done to me.
You know, and then calling my family, it was last year,
and she called them, I guess, and I think in August
is what they said, August, because I was confused.
It's like, what are you talking about?
Cause I don't look at her wiki,
but she called them about it and talked to my youngest
So, but yeah, we made up and stuff. So I don't know. She's just insane and then Sam and I thought his channel was clapped
Somebody saying that he's streaming crystal because I was on there about him
Oh, he's gonna lose everything. There is a way to to report it and there's a lot of steps to it
Psyche and I'm gonna do that. So I'm glad because somebody's streaming him and showing that so it could be reported
Yeah, but yeah, it's just insane, but you know, you're a good guy
You appreciate you and you do the same like most of us we give people chances because it seemed you guys were good friends
And why does she just turn on on everybody?
I don't know and it's like
It's it's hurtful and it's
Confusing and it's very
Very because like because we're fine. We're fine. We're fine
It was like, you know, we were friends like last year August to December and then we like then
December something happened and then we were like beating enemies from like December until
April and then I apologize on the air and stuff like that and then all of a sudden
We're good again
Yeah, I guess she's bipolar and in her mood swings because I remember the first time she called me this last time
We were on the phone for hours that day. I was huh with I
Was getting the flu and stuff, but anyway, yeah, we had a nice convo and
Then the second time we had a nice convo the third time she sounded paranoid
You know and I felt uncomfortable and and you know just is there something wrong?
It's like get medication. She tells all these people you need to get help. You need to get medicine. She needs to
You know and then the video that she made before on the live and they
Clipped it where you know they sent it and that's where she's dancing
She's all drunk and and she was talking to her nephew who was in chat and she told them
Oh, he's watching and she was doing this dance and they said he was a minor
He was 15. I think at that time or 12. Oh 12. They said I
Mean, that's insane. What's what's going on with her? She she needs to get help
She's on YouTube. I mean all day all night
You know, and then she's just slamming people and lying about people and you know, it's just crazy
Yeah, I don't know if it was like he got mad because I was like streaming at the same time
She was or that I didn't like
in her being or something that but like are you are like she's like not just
saying no we're all working with Carl and Mimi so do you even know Carl no I've
never met him they said Carl was afraid of me so no I've never come he was he
was in her chat saying he was gonna contact me and Barb was in there that's
before she blocked Barb for the hundredth time he was inviting her but he
never went live you know he's he's weird he's a piece of shit and I think he's
No, I don't know him. And I don't know Mimi. I knew she was fake.
She tagged me to get on her panel and and everybody laughed like Kate.
She was laughing and she said that she tagged me and she said,
and I and Hicks wouldn't join. She blew her off. Well, I didn't know her.
So now now I'm involved with them. I don't know those two
I just seen Carl and I clipped Crystal when she had him on there
Yeah, because it was interesting and I heard about him, but I've never talked to him or anything
I would say that the whole thing is that we were trying to that day
Like we're trying to get the attention away from Carl and Mimi and her story about them
Because we're protecting them and we're trying to
How how would would I be involved with that when was this I don't know them you because you went live
Oh, because we I was we were on your live
Something about Carl full and and psyche and stuff like that and then she makes threats to me say oh well
You know someone's gonna need to step in and she won't say what it is
But like you know with that something's gonna need to happen to me or me just leave her alone
Hey, why I mean she's just got to go. I mean if you're mad at somebody talk it out or
Just stop talking for a while instead of going all the doing this in public or whatever
I mean, and she's well-known because now I'm being reached by all her ex-enemies that are sending me clips like the one her for pulling the knife on Donnie
And guess what that guy that she talks about Donnie, whatever
His wife is on and she's the one that said that she threatened to take her baby
And I said your baby how and she said well if you had that video before I
Said it that she threatened to cut the baby out of my stomach
And she was pregnant and she had the kid
So she's even watching but you know what I have a private investigator friend that I've used before in the past
I'm gonna give him a call. You know, she's going too far. This is ridiculous. I got attorney
She always makes these threats and nothing happens because she can't do shit. She works for Amazon
Customer support, you know when you call Amazon support
That you know, she's she's those operators. Maybe I'll call them and let him know what she's doing
You know, this is gone too far. It's like shut up leave us alone
I won't mention you stop mentioning me and I could kick myself for even giving her a third chance
You know and then her sister man shit. Yeah, I'll contact her but she's just gone too far
She contacted my brother. Why shouldn't I contact her sister?
I don't want to go that far. I just want her to leave me alone
I'll leave her alone just move on go your way. I go mine, and that's it
You know and she can't do that. She's got to do this shit and everybody says she's crazy
And they go along with it and they laugh and everybody says oh, she's gonna flip flop blue flip flop
And then you got chicken Andy on there saying I had a profile with a Dana name that was on Instagram
Years ago
You know, I had my own and I wasn't going to use my real one with these people from the internet and
Gia, you know, I have proof and Nancy's my witness that she was blowing me up at works desperate to talk to me using Nancy
To connect me on the phone and I took a break and I talked to her and then I said I got to go
I'm at work and she started screaming don't don't shut up and when my boss came out of the office
He was loud and he goes what's going on is that your phone?
I said yeah, he said please turn it off or turn it down because we don't want these other
Offices complaining because it's pretty loud because she was screaming me to you know to unblock her number
And Nancy was a witness and Nancy remembers that to this day, so yeah, it's just crazy and that's what chicken cakes who
Alex called a coke head because she kept her head kept dropping and
We were laughing about it. She was upset now chicken cakes again
It's trying to bounce back and you know Alex will take her back for a minute
Until she's done with her because she can't stand chicken cakes
And and I'm good with Carissa me and her cool. She's never done any of this. I respect her and that's why I supported her
But yeah, I don't know. What would you do a psyche like in my place?
Just I'm already gonna make another account move everything because I have my premium there now
Yeah, my brother probably add me to it because he says if you just delete that channel right now
We'll just put you on our family premium
Yeah, you know, so I might do that. So yeah, cuz he sees and you know, he was a dangerous hacker and doing all this shit
And he's he he's mixed up with police and stuff and he gets things going. So she's fucking fucking up
Yeah, yeah, I'm just done with her. It's like leave me alone. Stop stalking us
I would like personally like you know it's like I don't know if she wants to fight or it's like that kind of thing
I think certainly like we can all give a fight, but I think like the thing would be probably be just to not fight and
to let her
Work her right out of it. I mean it's like because we can't really do anything in the meantime
I mean with the in terms of like, you know, she's not gonna be convincing her there's not gonna be talking to her
It's like she just
Does it on her own and you know what had happened? She was already doing this stuff and I got upset so I blocked her
I did that I blocked her everywhere
She had my text now number not not my real number always. Oh you got my real one. No, my number starts with two eight one
That's a huge Houston main area code. The other ones three four sixes eight three two
They've got a bunch of those in text now, but she has that but we've called then
I'm glad it automatically recorded that on on there you know because I have the proof and
and that's how I have that recording of her talking about her sister wanting to sex traffic her
and I have all of that and there she's trying to post voicemails when she was trying to report me
And then she changed a link and I'm gonna fix it so she can be reported. I mean she was thrown out of Twitter and
Man, it's just insane
You know, I don't know what to do. It's like leave me alone. I'll leave you alone
She keeps going going going like she has no life
Yeah, you know, so and she doesn't know anything about me, but she lies on everybody. Oh, you're a coke head
Oh, you're this like telling my brother. Oh, yeah, she's doing math
And he's like, oh, that's how you've lost all that weight through through the years and stuff
And it's like no, I've never done math. I'm you know, and then now he knows
But yeah, I was you know, we had a falling out when I was in that hospital
over it because of her
But I don't know psyche. So what are you gonna do? Just ignore it. Just I know what do we do because she's going at you, too
Yeah
So just ignore it because she keeps going on and on and on and I could post a picture of her that was sent with her with
The sign asking for help because she lost her job and
somebody that she's
Tagging is the one that spread it to us even the one with the social security. I have proof where it came from
Yeah, and she's trying to involve him when she already knows from other people
And she was not want to fight, you know, it's like she wants like the back and forth and then the controversy
She doesn't have real life friends. It's like did you I've noticed that everybody said that she doesn't have any real people around her
That's why she's paranoid and walked so fast to the store when she gets out of her car
Like Tommy said like she's looking for people to come at her
She's probably been like this all her life and made so many enemies
It's it just doesn't make sense. I just want her to stop and leave me alone
But she yeah, she was on there saying that you I've been calling her the other day and then you called her yesterday
And it's always when you need money that you called her yesterday and you asked for money
These he lies that's why you you got to record everything with her and I'm glad I did
Yeah, I've never asked her for money once and if she produces anything
Which is a contrary
Like I'd like to see that because I've never I have all the text messages with her and I've never asked me to and then she lied
You said this and that and that no, that's why you're recorded bitch
Right, I mean it's like sometimes we have like no recourse because it's like, you know, there's no evidence
But it's like so it's like, you know, because because there's accusations and
Threats and all the stuff being made we have to document or keep them documented at least
Wait a minute is they'll done chat. I haven't been calling beta
That's some of her ex-friend that wanted to talk to her maybe because they mentioned that they wanted to talk to her
I'm not calling beta at all. I don't talk to beta
Sorry, I didn't see I was like it's in the chat. It's highlighted or whatever. Yeah, no, I don't call her
You can give him my text number to show him that I yeah my my number
It's it's a yeah, my text is a 346 number
Eldo, I'm not calling anybody my text now is 346
That's why it's recorded though. So so if I show the record and when I get her from beta and
From from before not now. I haven't called her in a while
Yeah, because she played it and she was on live with RG and we could hear you
Her recordings and the stuff she sent
You know I can do that and you know and I guess yeah
She's and I know that one of her ex-friends wanted to talk to her
And I guess that's a bad idea because she'd like what she had to say about one person or whatever
No elder. I'm not calling her those are old recordings and it's probably a voicemail
I've never put her out there. I can and her text where she's sending me
Some court information to turn and to turn it Alex. I'll go ahead and post that
But she goes back and forth she's a drug addict and she had issues on IG and all of us been through that and her ex-friend Jamie was in Barb where witnesses where she lied and said she once wasn't in that group chat hitting on this woman named Ashley Ray getting all graphic and Barb even said yeah I remember that and her other friend Jamie said the same thing yes I was a part of that group because in
Yes, Ashley Ray Ashley Ray they used to have a
Yes
Social Dilemma social Dilemma
Yeah, they know you know what ask Barb and ask Jamie. They'll tell you the truth
They were there because she was in there asking me was I part of DX when I first saw her because she joined later
I didn't know who she was
And so she joined later and she, you know, voiced the enemy at that time, asking me if I'm DX. I said no. And she goes, do you know them?
I said, I know who they are. And she gave me, she was like fake crying. You know how she fake cries?
And she said she wanted to be part of DX. And do you know, do I know somebody?
She always was looking for a group to belong to because she was always bullied is what one of her other ex friends said that she grew up being bullied.
I'm in in a chat that yes, she was on the phone with Vita and
and that's when she was at the other apartment and
Vita they were on the phone and Vita was complaining about some noise from outside
You know like because they were doing work outside. It was noisy
And Jamie and Jamie told her she said call your apartment manager right now and and tell her you need to be moved to another
Temporary unit until they finish the work
And so she she called the manager with with her on the phone and she heard the manager tell her
We can't move you to another unit because you're in a section 8 housing unit. Oh my god
That was prior to where she got now prior prior. Yes where she went to now was where her sister who's disabled
Lived and they are not close at all either. They've had some kind of falling out or something
All her ex-friends there. They'll say it because we talked about it yesterday
And, and they explained that she moved into her disabled sister's place, and that was
a place that her dad had years ago, and so the sister was there, but her sister moved
in with a boyfriend or husband, I don't know, she moved.
So all that proof will come out if she wants to go there.
So the disabled sister moved out and beat them up then?
That's what you're saying?
Yes.
Yes, that's where she's at now that that was her her dad's place from years ago, and the sister was living there
But apparently she got married or had a boyfriend and and she moved out and that's where Bita moved to
Now be honest with me Karen
Did you did you give Brandon Q?
Beat us telephone number so no never no he doesn't have her. He's never mentioned her
I didn't even know if he knew about her. No never. We never
He's been harassing her on her on her phone, you know, so
He's gonna come back on here. Although ask him I've never talked to him about it. He never mentioned her to me
Now are you and Brandon of cool like Gorgia or whatever?
I don't know what's going on with that it was um it was um um Alex who told me to support him and
he's a good guy and you know and she and and that and I did I gave him a chance she got us to talk
and oh and he's he was cool and all in and that but I know he has anger issues and I had a problem
with that yesterday it's like you don't have to be abusive or you know like that and and then we're
Yeah, he's freaking out that I was talking to Ganville on Crystal's panel.
And all of a sudden Brandon Q freaked out when he was talking to him behind the scenes.
Yeah, so he got real mad, told me go die and stuff, but he was just mad.
But I understand that because this is what happened.
All these other people are going to enemies and shit, so I can understand that, but that
was a little too much.
But I understand how he feels because when we talk, he's a good guy, you know, and I'm
just sick of these others starting to shit.
Now, oh, ask him.
That's him.
He said that you're calling her a lot, Brandon, I never gave you her number, are you calling
Bita?
He's gone. Oh, he's got a site site. Can you drop the link site one more time? Yeah, drop it. Yeah
It's in there. I dropped it. Yeah, let him know Eldo cuz you're asking me about that and I don't I've never me and him
Never know what so what what now you want to talk my sister now? What's up with that?
No, no, nobody's back in your sister crystal just texted me that you're
No, no, not you I didn't mention you I talked about you did I played the live you say you want to stop my sister
You want to go real life?
Sister you piss me off with Chris O'Lan. Why you want to be cool with Chris O'Lan?
Y'all both weirdos
Salmon
You talk about your family now y'all didn't want to suck each other click
Salmon just that I'm not gonna go at any of your family. I was pissed off
You said it, come on, get out of here.
Are you a Christian man or buddy buddies?
No, we're not. We're not friends.
We're not in touch again.
I'm asking her. I never called her.
I never called her either.
Salmon, Salmon, Eldo has a question for Brandon.
Please let him ask him.
Brandon, just come back.
When
Nobody's going yeah
Little boys online
He's your sister's face
Why do you play you
You
Brandon, Brandon, Brandon, Salmon, Salmon can be an asshole, but he's not a pedo.
He was playing some game for a while, he was playing Yu-Gi-Oh with little kids and I'm
going to show them.
He's a pedophile, just like Gamble, playing with little boys.
Bro
Hey, why do you delete your channel when PPC was in New York?
Sucker punch you and blindside you dog just to let you know
They will fuck you up dog. That's why you deleted your channel when he went
Hey, I got all that you play you play with little boys on you
You play with little boys, bro. You my last little boy, bro. Yeah, get out of here.
There was one video of him playing a game and he was going to live. Yeah.
But Brandon, you definitely, you tried to forcefully kiss vegan at one time, man. That's kind of like
How is that forcefully if she's kissing back? That's not for kissing back
So she kissed you back?
Yeah.
I'm at the recap of it.
Well, they were talking to you later, though, though.
She don't even care about it.
She don't like to do it.
If she don't be here wanting to talk to me after that
and sending me nudes without me even asking,
why the fuck are you going to give a fuck?
If she don't even give a fuck.
Oh, she sent you nudes?
She sent you nudes?
Yeah.
She was cool with me the whole, this whole time after this.
I'm the one that cut off a few months ago.
I'm the one that told her I don't want to be her friends.
Two months ago that happened like three years ago that happened three years ago, and we've been friends the entire time
Okay
Brandon elder wanted to ask you he says beta is saying that you're blowing her up. You know, you're not never talk
Yeah, that's a lie. I don't need to try to get me arrested. They did that with Elisa Jordana
They were texting her threatening her saying pretending to be me
Although I can you know, I can show you my my text now number and yeah, it's it. No, I haven't called her at all
I haven't talked to her in a while
But Karen, which text now number will you show me you got about 50 and 6?
Yeah, let me get it. Hang on. I'm on my phone right now. Hang on a minute. Let me let me get it
At least know the area code of the one you use
The area code is 346
3 4 6
Crystal because she she got a text about
Yesterday back. Yes, I can give you that's well. It's a text now
You can you can put in any area code, but I use 3 4 6
Yeah
OK, yeah, I can give you the full number, but I'm on here right now.
Are you sorry?
What is it? Why does a sad man hate me?
But yeah, he's cool as they are, which they have work shit on him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I have proof of how he talks shit about him.
Now, he was telling somebody to stay away from him.
He's no good.
And then he deleted his channel when he was in his hood
just so he could be like, oh, like, that's why I couldn't lean cut, bro.
My channel got banned.
Yeah, he was clapped. Everybody reported him.
But I'm not going after his sister, you know?
I don't know what I said, but he was getting so hateful
and mean and stopping.
You'll say whatever you can, but no.
Bro, I'll bone his sister.
And he won't do nothing about it.
So forcefully, forcefully or...
Oh
In prison in New York that if you're in there for raping women and kids that they don't press you like it's not like
There's like oh, I'm in here for raping bitches. Like that's like
Close no, they don't know and don't lie bro. I know all about New York dog. Ain't you motherfuckers from New York?
Anyway, so why would you why would you know why would you know something like that?
Why would you know that they don't press me bro because I've been in federal prison homie
Oh, so you've done it before you had charges for it and they didn't press you
That's what I thought punk ass bitch. Fuck New York homie. Fuck New York dog
Just like Tupac. Tupac was in jail for raping a bitch in the ass in New York, and he was a god in there.
They don't give a fuck about child molesters. That's West Coast shit, bro.
And that was a prison prison. Yeah. Yeah
Kupak was in New York in prison in New York for rape for sodomy raping a bitch a
Girl in the ass
Kupak was in prison in New York for raping a 16 year old girl in the ass gang raping her Wow
They didn't even lay a finger on him. That's how New York motherfuckers roll watch the show Oz
Oh, yeah, they don't give a fucking being that you could be a child murderer or rapist all that in New York in the New York
System they don't care. They don't care. They don't care
They don't they don't I've seen that show 90 days
Okay, so another prison that's different in other states. It's where you have to show the gang leaders your paperwork to prove that you don't have no weird shit
Wow, I'll kind of like I'm in New York. They will stab you. That's one of the rules is you don't ask people what they're in there for in New York
If you're asking somebody what they're in there for they're gonna go at you. They're gonna you're gonna be the one getting stabbed
It's different. So what is he taught all these motherfuckers from you? Oh, yeah, that show the 60 days
I think it's called where they sent these
People they're in hiding and they go into these prisons and they see this horrible things going on and it's dangerous
I saw that but no, and I've never been to prison. I won't go to prison
But it was scary to watch that show is like damn. There's horrible things going on back you go
Don't know psyche. Where are you? Yeah, this is his show. This is your show
Yeah, I'm glad you told them be this line and saying that you're the first I was calling her no
That's not me and then probably doing that to make Sam and jealous. I bet bro because she
I was gonna give elbow the number, you know that the it's
346 number and be like me bro. She used to say oh so hot. He's so cute when I was streaming with vegan beatry it
And then I try to join her panel. She's like, oh, she's all don't be mean to me
She's like, I don't know. She's I'll go be mean to someone else and her name is spelled B. I. T. A.
That's be to make that man jealous. Probably say oh Brandon keeps calling me just to make by trying to make Sam and jealous dude
That's sad. Yeah, she's crazy the lion saying she's getting calls
It's show the calls and maybe you know, let it play on the voicemail. I always leave voicemails
If I'm calling somebody and they're not there, I leave voicemails.
And she knows that because she posted some from a long time ago and I have a lot from her that I didn't post.
And then she thinks Alex is going to be cool with her when Alex can't stand her and she's just I guess they she sees that she has all the
Some followers, but that's the way Bita was she wanted
She thought she wanted to be accepted by groups because her ex friends said that she was bullied all her life because she was from
Iranian and and the kids used to bully her in school
And that's why she looks for groups because she doesn't have real life friends. That's why she's
i'm live all the time even on the fourth of july she was still alone watching the fireworks outside
her window it's like why don't you go out with people and celebrate and watch the fireworks
everybody does that but her and she's on 24 seven almost and she's drunk most of the time
i mean so now she's wanting to do this shit with when one of her ex-friends liked what she had to
About money thing or whatever and she was gonna give her a call and talk cuz they used to be friends
But maybe it's a bad idea because you know everybody's saying she's not the same person
Yeah, and trust me Sam and she plays with little boys online 100% you just like gamble
Always hanging out and talking with little boys online, bro
Yeah, I only saw the video pin playing by himself the yugioh cuz some people some people are like that
They'll be grown and they like the kid games
Yeah, that's weird doing a live about it, but he was by himself. There were no kids there just because it was a
Mostly a kids game, and I'm sure other you think you're playing with you're playing another person
You're not just playing by yourself. No, he was by himself. He was doing the live. He was talking to his live
He was showing how to play the game of other videos. I have other videos of him talking to little boys and he sent me pictures
Oh, you cute. I
Just like gamble bro. He likes little boys, bro. No, I never seen that about him
You wouldn't last out here out West bro. Hey, Sam and you wouldn't last out here out West bro in the wild wild West homie
You wouldn't last bro, and then he's scared of Q. He only wants to go at women only
But when Q or Barry come on he disappears like he's scared
He's calling me a weirdo me a creep, but he's always bumping Tupac like I said Tupac raped a girl in the ass and
Went to prison for it. I didn't know that I just know that you're listening to a
Oh, Rest in Peace, Tupac. Samman, do you listen to Tupac or not?
Tupac was convicted, went to prison for sodomy on a teenage girl, bro.
He's a fucking chomo, dude. Fucking punk.
Come out west, Samman. Come out west, dog. Come out west, bro.
Mm-hmm. I want him to come out west, dog. He won't.
Yeah.
Fuck, yeah, no, he won't he won't deal with guys. He disappears. It's where he wrote all these dudes ran for me
Notice
He disappears and they went off on him even Tommy and he disappeared
He was busy yelling at me and KK. Yeah, see you want see how come women now, bro
He'll argue with a female, but he runs from a man
think probably his dad was abusive with the mom that's probably why and that's
what he learned and wants to go at women because that's that's why guys get
like that it was having mommy issues or daddy issues so I guess he wants to be
like his dad he lives with his dad and that's why they clipped him his dad
yelling at him to clean up or you know and
Uh, yeah, that's it. I still have that clip, but I didn't post it.
Well, who's your fucking sister? Now that he wants to bring his sister up, now I won't get a beautiful one.
No, no, no. Really?
Yeah, since he accused you of that, then, then, then okay.
I'm not gonna call his sister. If I said it, I said it out of anger. I wasn't...
Oh, who's your fucking fucking sister, bro?
Dude wants to sit here and call me a pedophile? Fuck him, dude.
Man...
You're getting more views than Sam and now bro. That's why he's mad. Yeah, that's probably why he's mad
You know and his channel was struck down and now there's a way to
For bane evasion. It's a long process too, but it does work
We did it to a big streamer and he's pissed off. He lost all he had four channels
And it worked, but it's a long process
You have to put in every link because they'll know it even if they hide it because he had one
hidden for a month
And then he then then he was on somebody's panel bitching they took everything and all this shit and you know
Fuck you and all, you know, he can't get on
No, I don't know if it's his ip or something. He can't get on and he was just going nuts
Screaming yesterday on somebody else's panel. It's like why are you even on?
If that, you know, they banned everything
And he was making a lot of money and that's what he's pissed off about and salmon that's gonna happen to him too
Everybody reported him and that's how that channel was taken down. I just want to know why he will heal
I've literally watched his dude sit there for hours from the from the Sun set to Sunline
But once he's once a man once he hears that that man voice
He shits pants. He shits himself.
Yeah, he shits himself and disappears like he's a freedom man.
And they said when that happens that's a something with the mom
I guess the dad abused the mom and that's why he's abusive towards women because cake KK and I still have that clip
I'll post it where she said he called her
450 times a day and when Kate said are you oh she called you 400 times and she she chatted
450 each day yeah
Tell those dudes to come back it and I'll hop off if they want to press you
An old lady then then come back and I'll hop off
I'm not even that low old and and they won't even make it my age. Look at him
And I don't look my they wanted to go out or at a woman
They were
Going back and forth, but then he has a mommy issues. That's why it's all and that's what Barry and them said that he just goes
At women and he's scared of them
What did dead sectors say?
Who would that dead sectors psyche? What did he say?
The debt sector said a bunch of things. Let me see. I can go back to it. Hold on. It's like, it was like, oh, here we are. This is this is their show now. He's just a bunch of friends talking.
Yeah, I know 100% for a fact that that's his all. Yeah, he's that's communicate with me, bro.
Yeah, I can tell you what it said. It said, um, I'm going to have to go live. Okay, so it said, um,
And I don't know so I don't see it anymore. I guess it's it's deleted. Oh, yeah, it's cool
It's probably just something they just deleted it. Are they deleted it? Wow
Or it's a oh here it is here. It says dead sector said
Yeah, this is too weird. I'm not giving this old great this and bitch as a predator you to view and this is
Your view homie we the next person will view it bitch
You know you can pull up the alts too, that's that's how we found somebody y'all know and the another streamer called them out
It was three people. There's there's an app and it'll show you who they are you got to pay for it though
And plus I have a friend that's a private investigator
That comes through and has in the past and finding information. You can't find you got to you know pay him
And he'll do it quickly
Yeah, guys, I'm gonna take a shower and watch
There's more people are gonna come as soon as I get off psyche
More people are gonna come on. Yeah, now they're scared and now they're gonna like they like for a little bit watch
They're all they'll hop on I'll be back
He doesn't if you don't want to stay live cuz I'm done with this. This is too much though
I'm trying to be done with this. It's ridiculous all these nuts get alive and do some decent lives about real things not
Crazy drama to fuck with people
So, yeah, I have that process and I'm going to share it with somebody that Sam and those
because they're asking for that process because, yes, you can't renovate and it happened to
that guy.
It took four days and all his channels are gone, even the hidden one he had, and so he's
losing his income because he was making a lot of money at all these donations.
Why did people take his channel down?
No, we did because he was fucking with somebody really bad and and so she asked for help and somebody
You know needed it especially to report
All the other channels and it's banevation and it's a process that they got from YouTube a while back and guess what it worked
It worked. I didn't think they would take them all down
I thought that one that was hidden wasn't going to be taken down and and he was on with somebody yesterday
Streaming and shit and saying all of them were taken down and that that was his income
Well, I have something, you know, I'll show you how yeah, you just do it and and he's gonna get that
Innovation and then they can't get on again
Unless you have a different IP maybe
Yeah, because that guy can't get on and he's been a streamer for years
He's he's what a big streamer and he's all pissed off and and all he could do is join a panel
Well, let's watch something sweet for a second. Okay, short and sweet. Oh my god. How cute
Bad boy, bad boy would like this because he takes care of chickens. He's grown baby chickens.
How cute
They think that's the mommy. Yeah little little little chicken McNuggets there. I think chicken McNuggets
It has a lot of trust for every cat has all these chicks. Look at that. Oh my god
oh my god they're so cute where's the mama chicken i guess i don't know if you might walk in i hear
your oh there's coming soon oh no oh okay good look they want to
oh they're so adorable the guy's getting away oh i hear it i hear this is adorable
oh she she loves those chicks it's so cute hi lanora that is just amazing
If I think that the mother I think oh no, that's a male. That's a rooster
Yeah, that's a male think roosters are those with the red on the top of their heads are just males
Okay, they but not be me a female. Okay
Look at the mouth open. I think oh no, it's not that's it. Oh
Look at that cat too
That's cute. I think it's gonna be like India or the Philippines or something. Yeah, we're all born together or something
But imagine like the trust to like even try these. Look, yeah, right?
They call it a hand though, but I thought the roosters only have the red thing on top when they're grown like that
Is that the same cat or is that a younger cat? Oh, yeah
the chicks stole the bed. Oh, so that is a hint. Okay, so they can have that red crown on top.
I think maybe the males have one coming down from their chin or something.
That's right. There was something different that you can tell. Yes.
And look at that cat over there. What a beautiful cat. I'll see they were hungry.
I mean, take care of these chicks.
So that's the door.
I like those videos that you post.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Sometimes maybe you do join a panel with, I don't know, because Ambeda's ex-friends,
one of them especially, the one that witnessed her about the Section 8, said it again the
other day, yes, it's true, I was on the phone with her and so did Barb about, and then about
Um, would you join when Barb is there so she can tell you to and then the other friend is gonna probably hop on
They don't get along so they can talk separately to you about beta
I'll see. I mean, it's like, you know, I like I I went and I like was I gonna see I I'll talk to anybody
I don't I mean I'll go on any show. It's not me trying to like oh, okay
I'll let you know you know what I might try to go live because they asked me to do it
And I've never done the live thing, but I'll talk to you about that because one of the
other ex-friends said, I'll only do it if you drop a link for your YouTube and I said,
I don't like doing the live thing and I've never done it before and I'll figure it out.
I know how to get on there to start it.
And as the other things about mod or people or whatever I never looked into all the other stuff
But maybe I just don't like going going doing live because there's a bunch of crazy people trolls
I mean you see people that killed themselves and they don't care
It's like they bully people to death and they're horrible people in real life
And that's why they're on 24 7 still doing this shit. Well, yeah, I mean I get the I mean it's like the trolls are like
You know they're coming in they'll say
Oh, get a job, right?
And then it's like, if you don't have like a job,
but then if you do have a job, they'll say,
well, you're not a real streamer.
Like quit your job.
Oh, we're gonna call your job.
Yeah, or yeah, we'll get you fired.
And like, I mean, it's like,
I mean, it's like, people get like so invasive,
especially in the communities like this.
So it's really not a good community if you have kids
or if you, I mean, it's like anything,
they'll just,
Yeah, the kids get doxxed and then they get,
then they start going after them or pulling up.
mean it's it's insane it's just stupid but yeah those trolls are the ones that
are on forever always hopping on all these chats or panels I mean no jobs
it's like don't you work during the day or night that you're on 24 7 if you're
not doing these long 10 hour lives or 20 hour lives you're in everybody's
chats trying to get
People to come follow you because you have no job. I mean, that's like salmon. He's on like 24-7 and
Kate mentioned him yesterday. He's still harassing her, but he's scared of Barry
He's scared of Tommy when they start talking to him. He disappears. He only goes off at the women
So there's an issue there about his mom and dad. So yeah, that's obvious because if you look it up
That's why so it seems that his dad was abusive to the mom
Very feminine. Yes, and he doesn't act like a guy and he scared the guys and he still praises Barry who?
Who calls him out everywhere?
He goes and he even did on that live and
Sam and acted like it it didn't happen and and that's why I clipped it because he was blaming me
And I showed the live this is where it came from this is where your pictures came from because they showed it on that and he acted like it didn't happen and then sometimes when I'm showing everything I was told that when he's clipping it, he'll cut off the part about him.
Right, you know, and then he'll go to the rest and and everybody there saw him do it
It's like wow this he's there's something I mean most of them
I guess have serious mental issues
Well, I remember like when I had like they played the beta that when beta came on and there's was like cooks me and like J
Why won't say oh remember you can cook sake you say you said, um, what do you what she say?
She said, oh, I'm a vigilante. I mean it was like the dumbest cookies. I mean she couldn't cook quinoa
you know, a rock and wall dish. But anyway, she um, like, um, they took that video of like, you know,
it was basically a good conversation or, you know, it was kind of a back over when we were fighting
and stuff. But they did that. They made me, they kept playing this AI video of me like dirty with
She was came and I'll drunk on white claws drunk as a drunk drunk. Yeah, she's unhappy. She's miserable
That's why she's drunk all the time. She lost her ex best friend curly
And that's weird because somebody that she knows was talking to her not me
But it's somebody that she was close with had been talking to her and that person was finally done with her
She said it was just too crazy
And then her her ex Kia was messing around that he went to the massage parlors and he was messing around with with the women there
The workers there so he wasn't really there for her like she said
But he'd always yell in the background about her being online or on the phone too long
Oh, you're talking about her ex Beyonce or something. Yes. Yes that guy Kia. I supposedly doxxed him
But then again, he's on Instagram KK had already shared his Instagram page
KK shared an Instagram page
She was cool with beta. So she went and gave it to you. No, no, this was before this was before she
Oh, yes, maybe they were fighting at some point, but she had actually already
Doxed or whatever supposedly beat his book be does Max Beyonce the thing is it's like I'm the only one beta's ever struck
We know she's never struck anybody else. She never got mad at anybody else over
it's only me beta also like she knew about like I had a porn bomb that I accidentally had put into a short and
And she saw it and she didn't say anything to me. So she was like definitely
She's like well, I guess she just hates me or something like that like
Well, she's always pretty much talking you and coming in your chats and trying to join and
Because I remember she was in your chat that day. It's like
I don't know what's going on with her. It's just she's and she's very controlling
She's the one that would be patched in the calls and stuff and and then she showed me how to see a third call
coming in. Oh, the other thing I wanted to say that time when Crystal called her,
we both called her, you know, and, and, and Bita answered real quick. And then Crystal told her
that I was on the line and we talked. She didn't sneak me on there. She told her, she said, oh,
she's, she's on the phone right now. And she was already in a bad mood and
crying about whatever was going on with them and then later when she gets mad she says crystal
snuck me in no she we were already on the phone and she patched her in and told her immediately
she's the one that sneaks people in and would use sherry to do that and talk to all our enemies and
But if she wants me to show all that I will I mean I have all the stuff from when she joined and also I did find that chat from
the one she was hitting on on
Ashley Ray and her ex-friends what one of them wasn't and wasn't on
You know, we didn't know her at that time, but the other one that was on the phone with her
She told me on the phone. Yes, I remember that and and Trisha would too Trisha was in there, too
She was in that chat, you know, she was in that chat too. So she saw
And she's gonna deny and say I wasn't there. I mean, you know, cuz you know, she did join later
We were on there before her nobody knew who she was
right
And she started hitting me up in DMs asking me if I'm DX and all this and I didn't know who she was
Yeah
And then I told Gia, you know, because she's the one that made that, that thing, you know, she, she wanted crystal to be 5150 like, like, like she would like she was, you know, beta and then and Barb is active she was on live last night she'll still stick to her word about beta.
Yeah, so I'll probably join her tonight and you know and we'll discuss beta and the truth all of it will come through and I'll also show that her DMs from a long time ago, especially when she sent me a DM that crystal sent her saying Gamble is trying to kill me and she sent that to me because she's shady and she was mad at crystal and she said, can you make sure to send this to Gamble but don't tell him where it came from.
And I said, okay, so just send it as is. Yes, send it to him. But no, don't tell him it's me
Okay, so I sent it as is with her information on top that it came from her her text
And then she freaked out later fake crying. Why did you do that? Well, you told me to send it as is because it was shady
You know, she should have just told crystal. She had had an issue with her
She didn't start any war between her
Gamble and crystal and gamble we made peace the other day we talked and
I'll talk to him again and he's gonna remember that that he got that because I even have that and and I'll show it on on
That live I'm gonna go ahead and join the live because he'll be on there
Yeah, and he's gonna remember that so I'm gonna show that if she wants to lie and said I'm calling her
Brandon Brandon. I don't think even those who she is
And she just lies. Oh calling me in place old recordings
I do have the recording that this other lady that she was scared of then she asked us to help her with her because she was
Stalking her and had Q go at her with her real picture
And then, you know, she like she's dangerous and stuff and then she was even in communication with her again, right?
Yeah, it's like the flip-flop. I mean, it's like, you know, but you know, but still like, you know
Alexandra can be friends with crystal again and gamble and all of a sudden and then it's then it's like I still
Um, can't talk to them or can't it can't go on. It's like I'm like it's like everybody else is forgiven or every
Always stays mad at me. I don't understand. I don't think so because when I mentioned you I
I don't remember. I never heard them say anything about you. You know, you could try
And listen, you know, don't take any resentments in with you though, you know
Yeah, I just went on the panel and then um
You know and then all of a sudden I
She was like well, why do you think I you can talk to me?
And then she kicked me off and then it was like and I was I was I'm banned in chats usually before I can even talk like
I'm like, you know for steens. I was I was uh, yeah
Next sometimes like, you know because people are making such accusations. It's like have your correspondence safe in order to like sometimes
Refute or to sometimes to show really happy because people can say anything. Oh, I keep everything. I have a few hard drives
I've saved everything since the COVID and it's mostly on my hard drive for my computer an extra hard drive
I can pull all that I even have some videos and
Yeah, I have a lot and a lot from beta. So yes, you know, especially where she was doing these jewelry and
making money off of
Um, I'm not not Amazon one of those
eBay I think
Yes, and I did see the proof that she was using Kia's information for
taxes for some reason
Yeah, she was reporting him because she told one of those friends that so what she was doing and she could be reported for for that
And it's all in his information
But, yeah, I've seen his profile on Facebook and they showed that she even did an AI image
of him to make him look a little different, but, yeah, I remember, because I got a lot
of those pictures that they sent.
Like I said, I save everything, you know, text, everything, you know, and you got to,
I'm glad.
That's why I come up with the proof everything is saved or sent to me by people that know,
Yeah, I can't believe she wants to be involved when I practically almost defended her and
Encouraged that one ex-friend that wants to talk to her again because they used to be close
Yeah, and she liked what she had to say about somebody else that would borrow money from her
And it would add up or whatever and that other person said she saw that and she said that's exactly true because I can show
Proof that that she did that to me too, but that person always paid me back later with interest
Right, so I don't know I'm being called right now like you know
Alex is saying I'm an extortionist and I'm asking for money or I called yesterday asking her for but first of all
I didn't call her yesterday. I did
Text message her and I read the text message I said and nothing to do with asking anything
I just said my door was open and I don't know what I did and then she said well
You know what you did your selfish your this your this your this and that was it and I was then I said
I said well, you know what? I was like, you know, you're my favorite
you know vampire alien witch or whatever and uh you know and she was so mad yeah she's still mad
yeah and i've made a video too i've made like a you know a nice video like not trying to do something
like i mean i mean i meant it i mean it's like it was like but um
It's just there's no communicating with her right there's no talking to her
It's like yeah, it's hard and I think she just went through a lot and she's a strong person now
That's one thing you know that I I mean all these about her though. I see them think the flaw is that
She just will turn on people that love her and then go to yeah
Back and forth back and forth and it's like and it's like almost like with the seasons like and then when we're to we go back
And forth with somebody she gets mad
Right and goes at you, you know it but it's okay for her to do that
Yeah, because you'd always say like she's like, you know, she was even trying to like tell Vita
She's like, oh you and thank you. She's like, I'm not gonna get the middle of you
Say and see you see you hated Vita and if any one of us would go there she would have gone crazy
And then like she went up on on Zea's after she bashed and trashed him all over the place and he won't take her back
I don't think he's he's a flip-flopper
And pebs out those are the only two people that I see that don't do this flip-flopping
Because they hold their stance and when she tried to join like nothing happened
Zea was rolling his eyes like he wanted her off and she's still chatting and pebs was looking at him and and she was laughing
And then she laughed and then they start laughing hard and there was he said all that wonk I'd bitch or you know
And it's like she still had a membership because she wanted to record some some
I guess some live of of stew joining and I think we I didn't even know what that was about
That's in text and I can show that I'll show that so
Well, she wanted that because they put everything on members only, you know, and so like, yeah, exactly.
So how am I going to see? I've never joined. I don't watch him.
I mean, I don't know when they go live.
I think it's really late, late, late at night, and they already made it members only so she joined it.
So she's lying to make it look like like I knew something about the Sue going in there and saying stuff.
It's like I'm not a member.
And he could probably straighten that out because he knows she's crazy and he could probably tell that to that guy Rick
What happened that night because she's just lying and tell stories and like the one about her sister trying to sex traffic her and she was in Michigan
You know, it's crazy. It's you know, I mean she can't even get along with her
Most of them I noticed have no relationship with their family
And I know I do and and I'm happy. They're my younger siblings. You know, we lost both our parents
And we're all close because I used to defend them when I was a kid.
So we're always close and always will be and my kid brother, you know, came over yesterday when my cat was sick
The day before, you know, I was really worried and so he came by yesterday with my sister actually
And then we went to go get Mexican food and we had a good day
So I mean, I'm I appreciate that I have that good relationship with my siblings
You see that you see this message on the screen that Brandon just said what he's saying
Crystal being attacked for having you on last night and they're saying they only
Brought you on to make me mad that they don't like you. Is that what she's saying?
Crystal is very two-faced nobody likes her
That's why she said she was gone, but she wasn't gone because I remember she had brought a tucky reach out to me
I'm a year and a half ago because Crystal was seeing my my YouTube. Yeah, and
You know and there's something on her on there from a long time ago and and I don't know
Crystal we're in Alex's chat last night. Um, who crystal and right of Chuckie. Yeah
Really? Yeah, Chris Lannan Bride of Chucky and Chris Lannan apologized to Alex and said, oh, I'm sorry about everything and you know
blah blah blah like you know and I can't I'm looking it up right now
I can read some of this chat because it was like oh is it up. I didn't see it
Wait a minute because crystal is acting, you know, you know like we're civil
I'm the one that shut her down and I showed the proof or she was trying to hit me up with different chats
uh you know asking me you know to and i was already done with her then.
And then she acts like i still want to be your friend what we actually want friends we were never friends like issues is calling me every day at the hospital.
You know, you know, here's someone what she was saying here because so this is from last night
And it's like that her stream last night was called a review of what let's let's a psyche being exposed for what he is
Was Carl? Oh DX and so she's right now. She's going over like I guess an AI analysis about me
I'm gonna put and so Crystal was talking about me
Oh, um, well, I'm gonna get to that in her chat. Yeah, I want to see that. I didn't know damn
So I'm but I yeah, I can't put her on full screen. So I have to I'm gonna put us
I'll put myself full screen and I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna
See if I can bring it up real quick. Okay
Okay, hon. I'm gonna put myself full screening. Okay, so this is a
Here's what she was talking about last night and I'll read you crystals messages in a bit since that night
Clumsy who hosted the panel where Mimi outlined Carl or Mike's abuse?
Well, I annex aka Karen Lattimer and branding Tana
Occurred a couple nights ago when I was covering the abusive behavior of
Well nights ago. I was taking care of my cat and I had friends with me. I'm the cat. I thought she was dying
Carl slash Mike claimed her daughter's quote-unquote
suck dick for crack
Okay, I do have all the clips reflecting this and I should add that he's also been very abusive and
problematic to a woman known as beta
Bita's kitties within these communities. Many of you know that Bita and I do not exactly get along
But she does not deserve to be treated badly by this man known as Carl or anybody for that matter
Since that night clumsy who hosted the panel where Mimi outlined Carl or Mike's abuse
Clumsy has deleted the live stream outlining Carl and has been physically stalked by Brandon Quintana
In addition Brandon posted a photograph of clumsy son, which I personally perceive as a
He posted it too. That's what Brandon said. She posted it and then deleted it.
Bottom line, Carl is being protected by the group Brandon is aligned with, namely I and X, Psyche and their associates.
Yeah, because that's a group that appears to believe abusing vulnerable individuals,
meaning women, children and or the mentally ill for personal gain is okay.
I don't know that Carl slash Mike claimed to see that that during the live stream discussion
I was recapping and we're gonna review that clip because I want all of you to hear what you have to say
That his past moderators were DX and that Ganville at one point was his managing moderator today
Ganville claims to take extreme issues with Brandon now someone has left me a comment
claiming that
Ganville was never
Carl a.k.a. Mike's managing moderator, which could be
Carl a.k.a. Mike is known as a liar. I'm still seeking his surname anyone who knows it. I would appreciate. Yes
I know it somebody
And I'm having a hard time knowing who's lying and who's telling the truth
So now let's go ahead and take that's basically, I mean, that's what she said about like basically we're protecting
Carl and Mimi that's why we know I'm the one that clipped it and I made crystal more popular with that and that busted
Carl because he told her there that he hadn't been on any other pan
No, he he that he wasn't on any other panel
And so I showed that he was on another panel and that was crystals because they they said he was on a different panel before that
so I see like in the chat I says it says um
It says okay. He's a brat. He'll turn on I an X watch
That's why is he a one-one and then it says Anita Blunt
I've been in DX for about six almost seven years first time
I've ever seen Carl was on YouTube a couple months ago the man is around us and then bright of Chuckie
Oh, gee bright of Chuckie says hi Anita. Hello, and then it goes then Goddy comes in the room and Goddy says hi
Alexandra these people are clearly unstable narcissists. Yeah, I thought he was your friend
Because just say your course of personal excellent exceptionalism if psyche can't see the value of the friendship that it's his loss
See and this other streamer that that called
Alex out and Alex got quiet a long time ago when they had her on their pan on their panel
Well, I guess she saw what Alex is doing and she reached out to me and so she went on
Did a co-host on a live with somebody else? It's well known
about Alex, and they were showing the past of something that she did.
Yeah, I don't know and then they were showing some stuff that she did and they used my stuff and and and they're they
were showing her channel and
Talking about her about how she's sick and you know and these are the people that she's terrified of she won't speak of them
But yeah, they reached out because one of them I actually talked to on the phone one time and I was you know
I was a bit sure it's like what the fuck do you want? You know and she and we had a real talk
And somebody yeah, I'm here. I know ghost is ghost here ghost. Are you here too? Okay? I'm sorry go ahead
Oh, yeah, my bad. I was to let you guys talk my bad. I mean, oh, no, that's okay. Go ghost. I like your eight of your avatars
Thank you
So yeah, I like it really cool. Yeah, so it's just stupid the back and forth. What am I doing? All I do is react
I'm not making calls. I did that before. Yes, because they did it to me
But no, I'm not doing the car doing it though. They know you're gonna react to it though. Yeah, you know what?
Yes, and and like good friends tell me just you know what fuck now
Because I got so much good things going for me now even my a good friend of mine that was over and she saw me react
Then and she was like
She practically turned off my phone and she said who are those losers? You got a lot good things going on for you
Why waste your time? I never have to work again. I think I went to though
I mean my family now my mom came for money
Getting good advice and you got a good head in your first yeah
And that's what that friend said look at what's going on your different person
And she said I don't like how you are on on YouTube and she said I want to tell you the truth
I've watched you get upset
don't let those weirdos trigger you. And then she said, do you know what trolls are?
Those are the worst people that try to push people in the
suicide. And you're just getting as triggered as they make other people triggered. And when
you're off of there, you're you, you're a different person. Right. And I noticed that, yes, and I
get triggered. And I never was like, when COVID started, it was Gia that got me involved. She
and Alex back down on her and then she had a lot to say to all of us about chicken cakes.
Well, it sounds like you're just asking for your own question. You're getting triggered
for no reason. You're crashing up for no reason. Listen, let them live their lives.
Don't do that. I mean, you're better than that. I mean...
Yeah, exactly what my friend said and then we had a great day and I left my phone at home.
Well, listen, you like to talk a lot, which is okay, but you don't like to listen.
Go ahead, go ahead.
If you listen to your friend, if you do listen to your friend, I'll tell you the same shit.
Don't fuck if you didn't do like trolls cause I am a troll.
Don't fuck and if you give me like one thing, I'll fucking harm under it and I'll keep doing it.
But if you don't give a fuck, there's nothing to troll about.
So just let it go, be cool, talk to it.
I mean, they will, they'll test, they'll test, they'll figure out, they'll see what
it sets you.
And that is, brother, early morning crash out on it, then they'll double down on whatever
it is, like with me with my cats.
Oh yeah, dude, hey, psych, once you let them know that it bothers you, they will bring
it up every time you fall.
Because really at the end of the day, I know my relationship with my cats, and I know my
cats love me and stuff, so I'm not bothering them, live, I'm bothering them.
But anybody with cats or kids, people who go after those, because it's like they know,
like there's no matter what, you're going to be triggered over people attacking your
loved ones, right?
It's like that's like everybody, it's like a normal thing.
And so that's kind of like the most obvious thing they can do is just go after that.
But it's like, so we have to really fortify ourselves and know ourselves and not take
It's all just to upset or trigger or to to shit-ster things
They know it's gonna trigger you that will fucking do it, but I do the same shit
If I know it's gonna trigger you and I want to get you going
I'll fucking say the same shit like because it's gonna bother you
But it just won't bother you be a grown-up woman
Put your fucking britches on you a grown woman and have a little respect for yourself girl. Don't let them trigger you
i'm sorry am i being too hard right now in my bed no you're being honest and that's good advice
yeah i gotta put it in my head and do that because i am happy outside of it and uh you know and like
i had it outside of it yeah i guess we did are you and turn it off yeah run that shit right if you
don't just fucking cancel them out it doesn't matter
Yeah, you know you're right that though they talk shit about me, but I want to argue I want to debate
I want to do all this shit, but we're different if you don't want I'll let them get to you come on
They are constantly called ghost gay because you know he's donating
Yeah, and you know what? I've donated a lot of money to a couple of them. Over $1,000, $1,000, $2,000, and I don't want to say their names unless they get involved in it.
Can you say who? Can you say who starts with them?
I don't think, one of them is AstroMom.
Oh my god
Resonate resin that only got 350 and the last time she called me
Would you donate to psyche? Let me see what you speak. Yeah now I should it just that I got done donating after being screwed over
You know and and uh, it's it's and I donated 25 dollars to Alex a year ago
Are they live right now? Let me I'll get them for you. No, no, they're not. There was a it was a
I'll I'll tell you in the chat because I don't want them trying to use her whatever, you know
Yeah, you know our ghost uh you if I'm p cartel on ig I can send you whatever you need there
No, we have it it's p e k e underscore
cartel c a r t e l
Yeah, and now it's private though, so I'm careful of who I add on there because I usually
Right now you're talking about spending all this money and you're being disrespected listen. Yeah, I'm telling you
I can show it. I'm sure like look at my page. I've showed my one of my cash apps for this year
You're literally right now. You're giving them what they want. They want you to yeah
Yeah
Yeah, I hear what you're saying. Yeah. Oh my god. I know way to crash out in real life
You know and and
That's good advice goes thank you for you know a psyche she has permission to crash out
Yep, you do we all have permission
Yeah, everybody has permission but not to continue though, right cuz
She's go ahead goes crash out
I
Listen you let the trolls get to you. Hey, yeah, and we're your business girl if it's not well
Why are you you're at the YouTube streets? It's the internet fucking this little shit back to them a little bit
You know what your right goes because somebody else that I'm close to
is was saying the same thing and that's somebody online i don't mean to bring it like this you
are female and i don't mean to bring it like that but you know i know more emotional a little bit
more emotional means just fucking dude if they want you to crash out give them a good crash out
give them a good crash out but don't be sitting there being emotional i'm like i can't believe
they've done this to me no fuck that they did it
Yeah, we're gonna win this one, you know, you know who I respect is that Carissa because I've talked to her
She never asked me for money. I've supported her before and I don't think it's fair what they put her through because look how successful
She is with her channels or channels. She used to have to hold up. Hold up. Wait a minute
You said they asked you for money
No, she didn't but they yeah, they would or hint or all you I'm so
You know, I
For yeah, you know, and I need
Psyche a lot of money never asked me for I've dissented
Yeah, I mean sometimes up to others. I just donated and you know and then and then only to them
So what you said a girl was they asked you for money. Listen. Yes, uh-huh. You know all of them
Let me explain it in like a little let me use little words
So like let me use an analogy if you don't mind. They're like a fisher. They're like a fisherman
They put the worm on their hook. They'll cast it out
They send that bait out. If you take that bait, it's your fault. Don't take the bait. Oh, yeah
Yeah, no, I haven't been donating to any of them, you know at all
You even being up there talking you're giving them a piece of your mind you're giving them time they don't deserve it
Yeah, you're right. You're right
Yeah, I'm just gonna be the better person and you know I mean I guess that's my final reaction then cuz you're right I don't want trash on there cuz I was getting good followers from my shorts in there and then I had.
Another channel I had like 1900 followers and it was mostly people from better places though like one musician and his wife
They have a big
Dog rescue place and and they do the lives and and make me beautiful music
And it goes to their rescue and they don't ask
If I would say something right now you're gonna react to it just don't react to it
But what the haters talk shit let the haters you're gonna hate you know that. Mm-hmm
Talkers are gonna talk shit. You know that
Don't do it and just down with one. Yeah
Yeah, I'm with them if you want yeah, I'm not done with them cuz I
I'm a shit talker and I like to fuck shit and I can debate, but yeah, don't feed into
this like trolling shit, come on girl, you know that.
You're right.
Yeah, you're right.
It's stupid, the lies and rumors and stuff, and I used to have a bad drug problem, and
I did some shit though, ghost for somebody, some screamer.
I'm not gonna burn right now, girl.
I'll fuck this whole thing up.
Oh, you know what?
I'm proud of myself.
I turned it down a week ago because I was heavily into coke.
There was no way I could say no for years.
That's not what's troubling you though. What's troubling you is like these YouTube streets and you shouldn't fucking give them to these fucking trolls.
Yeah, that's true.
But listen, if you're gonna give them to the trolls, you gotta troll back and you gotta be better.
If you don't do it, if you're not, if you're not trolling, don't troll.
No, I don't do the trolling.
No, but what I was saying was I had a bad cocaine problem and I'd be doing all kinds of shit during COVID,
but I could never turn down coke.
And that was one of the reasons I had moved out here, you know, a few years ago and I was still struggling with it.
But I was happy because I was at the pool and this guy said, you know, we were smoking, uh, weed. I had a question. I got a question.
Do you have a drinking problem as well? No, no, no, just drugs. No, that's, that's rare. Okay, continue. Yeah, that's barely, you know, I, I, I'll have a
margarita or two sometimes and, um, you know, that's it. I'm not, I never really liked alcohol.
So that's I'm lucky.
I mean, I'll have two margaritas.
I'm buzzed and I'm fine.
And it's not often to see.
Yeah, I don't go fuck.
I drink, I drink a whole bottle.
I don't go fuck.
Oh, really?
No, I'm not a drinker.
My sister used to be, but she quit that right after when,
right after my mom passed away.
She stopped all of that, but she never did drugs.
She was against drugies and was against my other brother
who used to be involved in drugs.
And she'd always bash him for it.
Then look at me. I became a drug addict I have two words, but she still respected me
She and I remember her friends would tell her oh tell me oh she adores you and I said is she
Disappointed about my drug usage. You know and they said no
So I'm gonna know you right now. It kind of seems like you're letting these YouTube streets get to your head
And you you're getting these trolls get your head you shouldn't wow so that's what it is. Yeah, cuz I've never had
Yeah
Well ghost, you know, you know, I think it's like like, you know ghost is ghost
I'm getting kind of jealous because why are you such a ladies man right now? I mean, you never talked to me like this
We're we're yeah, he's good. That's why I'm gonna accept him. Doxy. What are you talking about?
Yeah, but she goes I'm getting jealous because
You're gonna start dating I and X now just leave me
Yeah, you sound like a good guy. Yeah, you know, you're a good person. You don't find people like this much. She called me a good guy.
Yeah, from, I mean, the advice that you're giving, that's good. That's a good person.
Listen, I think you shouldn't let the trolls get to you. It seems like you have like, you stand tall and what you stand for.
I do.
Don't let them talk to you like that.
And that's why they get mad.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah, I should prove and if you're not a good debater that don't go over there me
I like the trauma. I like the drama. I like this trouble. I fucking live for a debate
That's what I do, but you you sound innocent. You sound sweet. You sound cool in real life
Yeah, listen ma'am I'm talking you said
You even said that your friends with you the same stuff. I'm yeah
Don't let them do that to you. Come on now
You don't sound like a troll, but if you want to troll you got a troll better
You don't feel like a troll to me, you know
This look that she go
You're all right
So I next what you look like real quick. Oh, it's real quick. Yeah. No, don't do it
You do it. I'm gonna punch you in the fucking face, dog
The image is a cartoon. I'm gonna punch you in the mouth dog. Okay. I'm gonna punch you in the mouth
I'm often I run one you do it. Okay. You want me to do it? Don't ask question dog
Oh, all right. I'll let that go. Yeah, that's cute
Hey, you like that picture? No, I like it. Yeah, I like the cartoon like that
Yeah, I like the cartoon picture now show it again. I like that. That's cute. You got a headphones on. Oh
No, that's your hair
Yeah, that's cool. Yeah, you sound you sound cool though, you don't sound like a troll, but yeah, I don't troll
Well goes like
You got me a little scared there. I didn't know what a picture you're showing. I say, hey
I'm not gonna show that your toe photo
Well, you know, there could be another time I come here and fucking crash it on you
But I think that she sounds sweet. I think that she gave into the trolls what you never do
Reasons you get into the trolls unless you're in a troll back. You gotta be better. You gotta be funnier
be greater. But if you're not a troll, you're not a troll. I mean, no, I'm a I'm a joker and
this is me in real life. Oh, this bitch Fiona. She's not cool. No, I hope you add me on IG and
I'll be showing stuff that I went through in the cast. You know, you'll see. And there's a one
I go well on IG I'm peak underscore cartel here
I go by grateful grateful and and I change it to grateful because
Can I say one thing mm-hmm you sound beautiful
I'm older now, but yeah, they're showing an old fat pic of me.
You're showing a little old school you saw in BISO? I like my woman a little bit old.
Yeah, now you'll see me on IG. I just don't do it here on because...
Well, I'm trying to see you right now, yeah?
Yeah, well, I'm not gonna do it here, man. Are you kidding me?
These people, and then they do AI and show old fat pictures?
Because then, when you're real fat, you even sound so fat.
Right, you know and I lost that that was in 2016 2016
Back up sake. Let me talk to the female dog. Come on. I want to show you something
I have a vision of your future and I'll show you hope it's not bad
It turned that shit off. Let me talk to you, you know.
Look at that dog. That looks like a Pekingese.
That's a Pekingese.
I'm giving her a good advice, though.
Oh, look at the Pekingese.
It's you and Ghost.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, and the Pekingese.
Ghost is a woman, though.
I know you're the female spirit.
What the fuck?
I'm giving her a good advice.
He disrespected me.
It's like, I'm giving her a good advice, man.
It is a good advice.
Oh my god
Troll right now you remind me of a Janet from three's company
No
She reminds me of my well you have my picture and that was a recent picture of me FaceTiming with some actually a year ago
Let me see that shit. Yeah, and that
Now in a real way
Okay
I teach her how to like fucking deflect the trolls easy work. I can do it. Hmm. I can save her
easy work
Okay, guys, I fixed it. I fixed it. This is actually you guys. Okay, ready here. This is ghost
I'm gonna post that shit. Oh
The piki is again. I gotta go for the friendly ghost saving these hours. Yeah, huh?
I ain't call you have by the way. Yeah, it's not romantic. It's beautiful
Beauty and the beat like cast for the Sunday
Have the ghost holding the Pecanese had the ghost holding the Pecanese. Yeah
I'm holding up your troll. I'm holding up everything. I have to send you because you might do all right
I have to send you I have a black because you get triggered by everything you're getting triggered by fucking people fucking over here
Trolling you getting triggered by everything. I got you back
Just like if we woke up in the middle of night, and there was a fucking armed intruder broken our house
You go to the closet. I would defend you as a man
So listen, you're you're letting everything affect you all trolls like you know these YouTube streets affect you
I don't really like it matter of facts like
Get her out of here. I don't even like her leave her alone. You better not go
You let everything affect you
Yeah, and I'm not going to yeah, you I started let me let me but it's not now because you're in my
Yeah
Are you listening to daddy? Yeah? Oh my god. Go. She's not gonna call you daddy. That's what that's my
She's gonna call me daddy before the end of this night. I
Fix it again. I fix it. This is actually you guys not this one home. This is actually you guys. I think it's this one
There you go
Black pecan ease. Yeah. Oh, yeah, she's my daddy from that picture
Access you
Explain can I explain yeah, go ahead? Yes, you would have never done these trolls
You would never done any of this if I was a part of your life
I would told you sit there shut the fuck up. You're not like listen
They're not important. They're talking shit. Just let it go
And you don't listen to me, but now you're here like all these trolls these trolls see you need it
You need a big ghost in your life. You need a deputy. Yeah. Well, I'm listening to you. That's the best advice
Relocated I think we have West Virginia in Texas. Okay, so are you guys far?
I'm in Texas. I'm in Texas. I've never been to uh, West Virginia. I've never been to Virginia.
No, let me go. Come over and coal mine a little bit. Yeah. I've been everywhere else pretty much,
even overseas, but never, never Hawaii. I've never been to Hawaii. I appreciate
Uh-huh. Well, you know
Starts with a T. I annex you like trains
Yes, I do they got them over here
Station right next to a trace. No, I said I was gonna move for her
You want to touch it on me, huh? Okay. He wants to go to Texas. You have trains in Texas
I think he'll miss the sound of the
Hey, do you have
Horse together that'd be cute to wash. Oh, yeah, I had we had horses my my youngest
Together, but here's a real question. Can you ride me? Oh my god?
Yeah, we're train station the train
Goes the question is can I pack your caboose?
You're gonna pack my condoms to fuck it. No, I'm fucking it. Yeah, I'm getting a kid. Yeah, bitch
Baby, you've heard Thomas the train now. We're gonna have Tyler the train Tyler the train
My name's ghost pussy
Ghost the train
that would go as a
Yeah, oh, he's watching me
Never mind my bad and you can see my channel and see what's going on grateful 2026
Well, listen, I think that you joined a lot of panels or something or a couple panels. Yes
Let me tell you how to react
I think that you react what you shouldn't react because females are really fucking they're emotional and they let's react to the emotion
But logically you wouldn't react the same way correct
You need a man to sit there and like hey shut the fuck up or hey talk the fuck up
No
It's not like say I'm like a the sky is blue and then I said the sky is fucking blue
It's not a tome police thing. I'm not if I take the shut up or if I take the talk
I'm give me fucking you look at that. That's an AI of me with bald hair and that's not me at all
You'll you'll see me on your on IG
You want me but I'm taking by
No
I'm done with with the relationships. You know the John that we broke up. He was going cold and I got clean
I can save her, I can save her, you know, and I just like to be single and me saving brother
You've talked a lot of shit, but you know other people talk shit about you. How dare you let people talk shit about you
I'm right
Now I got you
Okay, this is like I'm ghost. He's more like he's more like cocaine than ectoplasm right now. I think and
I'm a little cocaine now
Okay, he's not okay. Well, I don't know. I don't want you getting I don't want you doing cocaine around Karen
Well, you know what? That's what I was saying when I was a pain
Okay, I said baby girl. Yeah
Listen, is she from Japan?
No, I'm half Bolivia, and I want to get my panties white or white
No, they're considered white in Bolivia and they have Indians up in the mountains or whatever and then they have the white people
They came from Spain
He said you're your Japanese
Get out of Karen's Japanities, okay?
And ghosts, they keep reposting an old fat pick of me
from 2016, when all that weight's been gone for a year.
Oh, big girl, I like the B.B.
No, I was, I'm thin now, but I was getting diabetes.
I had high blood pressure and all that's gone,
so I'm healthy.
And and what I was saying is when somebody offered me coke last week
I said no, and I didn't feel bad about it at all. I wasn't feeling for it because you know
But I was I was proud of myself. I was happy and he respected that he apologized just
Beautiful you
Yeah, well, psyche is on my picture and that was a face time and I'll send it to you and then if you had me and I just send it to me.
I think he had it. I had it posted that's when I told beta to come up like me. Let's come up together and do a lot of panels never talk to you before I know that.
Yeah
Baby girl, I heard about you, but I think on on psyches because he's got some good legs
They're bad good or bad. No, I think it was good when you show you were there supporting him
I didn't see you trolling. Yeah, I was defending. I'm trying to find you though. Mm-hmm
Yeah, and thanks for defending him because they come at him hard, too
It's just ridiculous and he's done the same thing like me and take people back only to get fucked over
Well, Psyche can't defend me like I defend him because Psyche Psyche never judged that man, but I like to debate
Yeah, that's why. Okay. All right. Well, I'm gonna go ahead and go. I'm gonna go to the pool. Finally the sun's up. No more rain. So I need to get darker. I've been tanning. So I got dark.
Yeah, that's okay. No, no, I hope you know I do like I do like you guys met
Can I put him on Instagram? This is a nice a nice guy. He's a nice guy. Yes. Yeah, he's a good guy
He's a real person and it's weird because it's trolling and stuff like that
I've you know, you you don't have it in real life in real life. You keep your friends
I mean, I've had these friends since I moved to Houston
And they're real and a good people and they don't do this online thing and they get so mad at me when I do when they see me upset or triggered when they come over, it's like, man, you're late, you're supposed to be over.
Can I get your number in the back chat please?
Yes, I'll give you my number, so let me, yeah, let me, okay, let me put it, it's, okay, hang on that, let me go in there right now.
Si, can you, Si, can you post your number in the back chat if you don't mind?
Yeah, I might not.
Yeah, you're getting you're getting eight to
Okay, okay, hang on. I'm putting it in that's my number. That's in the back chat
I trust you psyche so you can take that number down
No, I said psyche to that I know you that's for you, but I told psyche he can have that number
Thank you. I'm going to write it down.
Uh, and, uh,
Look, look, now they're harassing me by phone.
Oh, calling you?
Yes.
Oh, it goes.
It goes.
Ghost is already harassing me by phone.
Oh, that's him.
Oh, okay.
I thought it was somebody else.
They said, oh, I'm sorry, coast.
I'm going to add it.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I thought it was him because the state said something different. Oh, okay. Yeah, I guess he he wants me to I don't know
Is he gonna come back? I just put it there so he'd have it. I didn't think he was gonna call
Well, I know he's already
Not no well now he's gone. You're gonna need to get an exorcist to go
Yeah, okay. Well, then that's my number psyche because we've never screwed me over and we can talk there
I don't give it out. Oh, okay there. He just texted. He's
Yeah, he's funny. Okay. Well, I'm gonna go out to the pool since I'm coming up and my friend's texting because they're about to come over
Okay, love you. You too. Love you too. Okay. You have a good one. Bye. Bye
Okay, well, I don't know if it goes back up, but we have 55 people here
Might as well
Nobody nobody run out. Let me see
What have I got? Oh, actually I did here's a sweet video about I can't it's kind of like bass on that song
You can go. Yeah, I'm way
Not song pretty good. We have it. I don't know
Let's see
What else okay, so I guess I'll just play my my look at me on
Looking video here. I love it
And then we'll uh, we'll regroup and we'll figure out what we're gonna do for the day. Oh, this is the separate waves one
Here we go. Next power couple you hear it for first
and symbols that's always been me but one thing pizzas was released without
charges what happened you're a man a new yeah yeah well you're so you're my
friend you're leaving me you're leaving me for i and x now she tried she tried
to you like leave me first like yes and no no no
I need to fix it. I need I mean, it's like I what is this you dancing at the woman with a peaking peat holding or peaking you
I oh, oh, yeah, baby. Oh, yeah, so I'm
You heard
Fucking idiot
You started
No
Can you tell me why everyone's talking shit about you on these YouTube streets cuz I made it baby
Yeah
In the background, you know, so I'm gonna screenshot it right yeah, that's my picture, but psyche sucks dick
So who's the worst off here?
Yeah, I'm gonna put psyche tea bag in you. I'm gonna put psyche tea bag you all screenshot it
I know
You know you guys, you know, it's um, it's 4th of july or what's coming up. Why would you do that?
Why would you do that if I didn't want it up there? Why would you do that, man?
You said do it
No, he's a man
Use on the other panel you'll stay away from my man my man my mom I was dying
Like I mean, it's like, you know, I think I have pictures of videos dick
No, he said he said the problem is if you send the dick pic back then there's a problem
That's what he said on the other panel
Right, and I didn't I don't send dick pics back because they'll be shared and stuff
And I want to save that for my my my ghost and stuff, but
Then goes talking all like shit. He goes join Theo's panel this morning. He's chilling with the guy. Oh, I think you
true
Did he leave?
Hello, what happened? Hello, bro. Is you there?
He's texting you, he's texting you.
He's feeling embarrassed right now.
Oh my god.
Damn.
Oh, hell yeah.
Funny as fuck.
What's up?
What's going on?
Playing shit.
What up?
I'm sure I'm attractive. Hey, where's your friend? Where's your friend? Remember your friend?
Yeah, you remember the big belly the other day is bald and he was like
He's at his house, you know, cuz you know
I said no, I say has nice
Yeah, well, they said to get his Speedos too. Yes
You see the speedos the other night I say I know I'm gonna try to like look around on YouTube audits
They were playing like, you know a replay I guess it was Harry and everyone was talking and then I
Come on
You were there I know everyone's eating and then and then oh 24 20s
Oh, that's gay. I don't want to see it. But then he played it on his show and he laughed and stuff like that
So I don't understand
Can you turn this camera off please?
No, you know, here's what I'm gonna do that though. I'm gonna do something for you.
Goose is dead, it's so jealous of Isaiah right now. Look, oh put a big screen.
He's jealous of you, Isaiah. He's jealous that you get to see your chest and not his fat chest.
Come on
Don't laugh at my ear like that you pussy don't laugh at my ear like that
Like you just gave you like relax relax. One more time. One more time. There you go
Show them the bear in me
He's not gay goes
Looks like a faggot. Hey, hey, hey ghost. Hey gay out goes
I think it's her it's a gay for you if bed you over break your back teach you what it's about
Yeah
I gotta try rejoin
See ghost, you made a beat
Why you made a beat ghost?
You jealous of psyching?
C'mon bro, you can't be running people off the panel like that ghost
You can't know
Go we gotta stop that shit
Come on here. Have fun and talk and you over here
Fucking panel like oh, that's my man. My man call the fuck down. We know
Oh man
Yeah, thank you. Thank you. You got a problem with you though. He's obsessive though down
Yo, yo
He's obsessive
Ghost you really obsessive like that to your boyfriends
Obsessive obsession. Yeah, I'm obsessed. I'll wash it down. Yeah
Yeah, let's take a ghost come on man back to fuck off him
This is what I'll do
Let's run it. Yeah, I'm just kidding. You can have him. He's a cheater
It's like he's a cheater, bro
Let's run this one. Yes
Oh, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God
I need some muscle or something.
I don't know.
Something, I don't know.
Fuck it.
The gut's still there.
Oh, yeah.
But, uh...
Yeah.
Do you look like you'd be good at like power lifting or something?
Do you ever do that?
No, I've never tried to blow something until it popped, but no, yeah, it's too
You want to try it on me or the shoulder?
I'm just kidding.
That was not going to work out.
I'm going to start going to the gym next week though.
I'm excited.
I'm going to get a membership finally.
I think that you should, I think you should not only go to the gym.
I think you should like, figure yourself working out and then do a flex show in the locker room.
And I think you'd get a lot of views.
You just want to see all the other guys in the locker room don't I don't mean I just want to see you, baby
I just want to see you. I mean, it's your friend. I want to see you and your friend
You're like I'm like lift of all those weight and like oh, yeah, then I want to see you do a flex
That's definitely ain't gonna be there
He's not gonna be there. Oh
Damn it. I don't know. Is he like he doesn't work out. Okay, but I mean
He's a painter, bro. He's a painter. He's a painter, but he's not a crackhead painter. He owns the company
I want him. I want him to paint
in my face with his calm.
Uh, okay, I'm sorry.
You know, I bet you do. It's okay. It's okay.
I was wrong.
He enjoyed the stream the other day.
Yeah, I think so.
He had a lot of fun.
That was the first time streaming, and I think he...
Jump in he got he fit right in he his shirt came up all of a sudden and then oh, what was the other day?
Oh, yeah, so like on this guy less was out in the street and he there's this black guy there
And he's like hey hey like you know
And the guy in the street he pulled out his pants and like with that as dick on the street on the side of the street
And like it was crazy and at least like whoa and I say and I saw because I couldn't take my eyes off it
But everyone else they even know they got porn about like I was like I was like well
He should he showed his dick and so um
Yeah, on the streets.
I mean, I need to move to New York, I think.
I mean, there you go. I mean that doesn't happen in California. Never it's never happened to me in my life
Oh, yeah, and we have ghosts back. Hey ghosts. You better not scare him away. Don't be scared of ghosts
You're scaring everyone away. So I'm scaring people away psyche. I love ghosts. It's okay
No, that's fucked up. I scared him away. He loves me. I ain't scared no one away
You're scaring people away pussy. I and X. I'm gonna crash the fuck out
Go so you're just talking to IA next
No, we're back up
Yeah, wait run every quest. I say it says can you film from an erotic sauna?
What I am fucking Sweden wake up fucking song. I don't know, but I know there's these black guys in New York and
They're like these muscular black guys, but they like they work out and then they go into like the sauna with like 20 other guys
They're in their underwear. They start doing push-ups and like cheering each other off
She was like, I can't talk a psyche poke shit about me. I was like psyche's gay
He didn't function by anyone. Are you sure you should have already loaded back up my back up often to crash out
I say when you go in the gym sauna, do you go in a towel underwear or nothing? I haven't been to a gym in years
He was here. Oh, I can't tell you the last time I was in a sauna
He's a fucking faggot. He wears hair next time you are
Can you film it and and send it to me privately?
I want to see your transformation. I'll go to a lifting videos. Okay. Thank you
I want you to be in like the double. Can you wear ultimate warrior out of fitness, bro? I can only wear what they allow me to wear
Please wear clothes dumb dumb. Oh good. Go ghost
Oh, and she might like. Yeah, I'm here. It's it guess what? It's so cloudy now. She's more sense of this fucking on this up here. Yeah, I'm gonna make us we're just caught. We just look at this hot guy in the chat now too. Is he hot? Oh my god. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
My chat one night and then I was like
Can I get a 1v1 Isaiah versus sir, they can get the one for all the all here you guys
Yeah
You guys
Fucking all right. Well hi nice to meet you. Wait you sound familiar me. Yes. I think I don't know. I've never seen you on a panel
Your voice sounds familiar. All right, maybe maybe you've seen me on somebody's panel because that was never on panel with you
I was on my going how's the night morning day. Oh fuck. We're in daytime
Cloudy it was supposed to be sunny now just nothing with clouds and now the pools closed
for clouds
Yes, because it looks like it's gonna rain. I don't know why they do that
It's it's one of the managers that does that the other one doesn't
Until late and they even lock it up like at 10 o'clock at night
But you know and not all the time, but it's like man, they used to be open all night and over here
Fuck that. That's stupid
Fuck that. Oh
Man, I'm sure there's a floor around here. Is that an AI of you back there in the back? What is better?
Is that the same one he had up?
No, and and on his panel behind our our
On his live on his live if you look at his life, he's got a
The background it's probably is a I think I'm assuming
Well, New York is with Hermosa Beach with 72 degrees
No, it's hot here just and it just been raining. I mean, that's that's the way the weather is here
It's bipolar weather and sometimes it'll just stop start raining when it's sunny
Same and now it's cloudy. Yeah, it's like damn
Fucking Ohio and it's hot and muggy shit. It was really day and now it's just just
Disgusting yeah, that's what I hate about here because it gets humid. I can't stand the humidity
That's where we're at. We're gonna have 90 every day next week 90 plus really see I think you're too
I'm not
Not fucking excited
You know, I can't stand the humidity here and people you know friends, you know, they asked me well if you yeah
They said the if you hate the humidity here, how could you stand it when you let I lived in West Africa and South Africa when I was a kid
And it's because we lived close to the beaches, so you didn't feel humidity over there. It was always cool weather
It's not like here that here. It's like hell. It's the humidity. I can't stand it
Makes sense. Oh shit
Yeah, it makes sense. Yeah, Bahamas was fucking nice. It was hot as fuck and then
Humidity was not existent
Huh
Oh my gosh, that's so cute! Yeah, that looks like mine.
You know what? On my channel, on the bottom, if you see a Pekingese, that's my sister's Pekingese Abbey.
And actually, that's Bita's voiceover.
And that's the one telling people, you know, do real life or something.
I don't like the drama or something like that.
And here we are, both of us, involved in a lot of the drama.
But it's cute. You should listen to it. It's on the bottom psyche and drama. No way
She's the one that let you cue at her house. Oh, did you like cue at your house or that dbo talking about who?
It says birding joint says she's the one that lets you queue at her house
I don't I don't know what let's you queue at her house. What does that mean Nick? I don't get it
I don't get it. We can start a line outside your door. No shit. No, I don't let anybody I don't
Give
People online any of my information I moved the third time
Anybody from the community in person I annexed you met anybody in person
No, not here, not on YouTube, but on IG, I have Facebook.
There's another big platform, MTV used to have a big platform and it was a lot of those
reality stars that were there and we all communicated together.
And there were a couple of people that I met on there.
And you talk to Aaron Carter. She like, you know, you were friends with him
Like did you talk about one of his dogs or something would happen? Yeah, that's why he got the pecanese gizmo
We named it because I told him that the guy who made the movie gremlins was a pecanese owner
And that's why he made the the pecanese. I mean, that's the gremlins kind of like have those big eyes
Like the kidneys and that's what it was kind of like based on a pecanese, but he made it like an alien
And that's what we talked about because he was following me on IG and he was putting all those hands up
Posts and he loved my dogs. He always posted to them and he said they were beautiful
And we started talking about it and he had these other dogs
And he was going to get another dog
And he liked my Pekingese, and I said, how about a Pekingese?
I said, the pug is not the lion dog like you said on your live.
I said, if you look up, if you Google it, you'll see the Pekingese is the, you know,
because the Chinese celebrate that they have a year of the dog and their calendars show a Pekingese.
When it here comes I say your how's your dog? I mean it's like he's okay. He's so yeah
He's quiet and all until I take him to my my you know my brother and sister's place
And he starts yapping like their dog Abby. She's out of control
And when I bring him back he'll bark a lot, but then he stays quiet. He's lazy and hangs out with the cats
Like right now they sleep a lot. He's sleeping on his back. And I see the screen boy. Oh boy
Oh, how cute that's beautiful. That's a laboratory or what is that? He's a Rottweiler in German Shepherd
Oh, no one okay. He did have the markets of a Rottweiler
and the color of the German Shepard.
He's beautiful. See, that's the way mine is. Chill.
He is very, very... Well, it's not very aggressive. I mean, when...
When a delivery driver comes up, he seems very aggressive. His bark's super fucking intimidating.
But as soon as you start walking up to him, then he runs away.
I mean it's me or my mother are the only two people that can touch him everybody else's fuck off
I had a pecanese like that and it was when I was a baby, my parents said they had a pecanese before I was born, his name was Chico and they said he'd sleep under my crib and he'd growl at them when they come in because I was all his and he was always protective over me and he passed away at 13, I was 12 and I was broken hearted, I came home from school and he was gone and they said, you know, he had cancer and they had him put it down.
And that broke my heart. And then I'd hear his, the chain at night.
We used to go down in the basement to play, you know, and we'd hear that noise.
So, you know, maybe that was a spirit because I've never heard it again after we moved from there.
But that's when we went back overseas, but I miss him so much.
Still, I miss him.
Yeah, that's fucking and he would mean to everybody else
He would bite my my siblings and it was just me. He trusted you know, I was his baby and he did love my mom
But they're good dogs, they're lazy though, man
They'll sleep like maybe that's why mine get along always got along with cats because they're lazy like cats
Oh my god, where did ghost go? He left. He said coming up. Yeah ghost is like he says he always hasn't that he's Tyler in the chat
He says baby girl. Don't let them troll. That's what he's telling you
Oh, I thought he was gonna be he said come on on panel cuz it's it's cloudy now. I'm getting ready to outside and now they got it locked
Ghosts come back up ghost and then go come on back up
Yeah, I don't want him yelling at me or whatever. I don't want to know why he believes crap or whatever that I'm not even doing anything
Yeah, those elder just like to stir up drama. It's kind of like that's his thing
He just likes to like, you know
Get all the right good taste in music
He made some song that he played that I liked and it was I I should have saved I have a new phone
I saw Eldo twerk before because um he um
He did a live and then he started he was he was having a ski mask or something like that
I mean, I thought he was a black man, but he's like he's like light skin
Oh, we have go it goes back and then he was that he twerks on the on his show
And so he's a tall guy. You know he showed himself one time and he's a real tall guy
It's all drink of water, right and and muscular. I think yeah, it's like man most of them are on
YouTube or you know skinny little guys
Wanting to bully people. I need some personal training from like Isaiah and Eldo and
you know, even say and say man can do an aerobics class and uh
I'll never leave that gym, you know, the Rolex. Yeah, I need to work on
Arms they're like too skinny though, and they've been like that for a couple of years skinny. Okay. Well, I
My muscles today
You're ready for this Isaiah. He likes it. He likes this. Hey ghost
How's that? Yeah, you're you're you're shaped so good. It's not like you're bony or anything
that they said I say look at that
It's a little bony but look but look at my belt. Can you imagine that?
No, mine. Mine will never be that flat. I'm not a great guy. Oh accepted it though. I don't want to flat
I like your tears of beer
You know what I noticed. Oh psyche. It's like my shoes struck again. It's like Dan. I was it
I went up to a size eight and then I was seven and then it went down to seven and a half now
I'm at seven seven now
I got to get new shoes because the seven and a half are too big now. It's it's I don't know. That's weird
I only wear crocs because you can you know the matter half feet how big or smaller feet cake
You can always just put a rubber band around really
Box are too sticky to cement though like when I wear them to go out. It's like shit. I don't need to fall
I just hit, Crocs are very ugly shoes,
but I guess they're like, you know, I guess they're,
or sandals, look at you, what are you wearing?
Oh my gosh.
Sandals I do, and not.
all day every day. I wore my dad's Birkenstock. I did my dad's Birkenstock. I like wore a whole
into the Birkenstock. I wore it so much. I like the van shoes and also the sketchers.
Those are comfortable. The sketchers are the way. Sorry. I think Rose Redd is Rose of
Redd. I think that's that person with PTSD and Butterfly or something. I hope you're
doing good. Yeah. So what Greek God would, what Greek God would I say it be? He'd be
Not promute that he'd be like, um, Hephaestus or he'd be like maybe like like a like a zoo
You're like a zoo's type. I just want to like kind of like, you know, sit on a cloud with you and you know, Orly Pleasure
This was into that though
No, but it's like I know you're not I know you're not but look at this guy
I kind of got you good. I got with like the muscle guy in the middle that kind of looks like you're a little bit
Yeah, that does look like him
Glasses
Yeah, that that looks like him
Yeah, I love that peeking ease though. I'm crazy about peeking eases like my family was my dad and mom
Yeah, and I want to see the real thing. You're so hot. I say thank you for coming back to my show. I thought you didn't like me
I never did not like you. It's okay
A lot of people turn on me and stuff, but it's like, you know, I'm super attracted to you
I my heart would be broken if you did that. I will I am forever a neutral person and I judge nobody
I enjoy being everywhere. I love that. I love that and you're my curious
I did not say that much
Never mind never mind. I can I can fantasize it. You should see what you can you should see what I do
Do I say in my mind? Oh my god?
Tell him
Yeah, naked right and then we'd be doing squats
But then I wake up, you know, I'll wet and stuff and so
That's all dream goes. I have to that then I have to run. Oh, I'm just kidding. Okay. Oh my gosh
I'm I'm I'm as I say gonna be my boyfriend. Ha ha ha. Yeah. Hey, I if he wants to be I mean
I say can I move in there? Do you have extra room in your garage? It's a big garage. It looks like can I
Know I'll sleep in the dog's bed. I don't care. You can you can you can chain me up in there and just have your way with me
How about that?
Hey, have you ever seen a dog in a sleep? Have you ever seen Black Snake Moe? Have you ever heard of that movie Black Snake Moe?
Yes.
Have you heard of that? Have you heard of that I and X? Black Snake Moe?
No.
I feel like I know him.
I think it's Samuel L. Jackson and he's the insert insider of his house and like and and and and I don't it's like terrible
I mean, was it a good movie? I don't remember it's a good movie. It's really weird though. I don't know if you've ever seen it.
It's weird.
I say why do you look like a tomato? I say you look like a tomato with curly hair. Are you blushing?
Means he's he's flattered. I think I don't like wavy hair. My hair is way wavy
Yeah, I hate that. I think I want to do have him do straighten it like the Japanese training thing
I think I forget where that place is. I want to do that. I hate wavy hair
Three-quarters black
Yeah, but so I like his curly I like I say his curly hair. Mm-hmm. Did you know that?
that he was. Yeah. No, I didn't know that. Yeah. More you know. No, no, I know. I said,
did you get like the black, you know, the big package? You know, talk about that. Yeah,
I want to hear about it. Tell me a little bit about it. No. Okay, he won't. Okay, never
Okay, that's personal. Okay. No, that's fine. No, that's fine. I didn't know it's cut.
Okay, that's all I need to know. Perfect. Christian Catholic background is good. Yes. Yes, and yes, I'll marry you. I will.
He asked. Yeah, yeah, you asked me that, right? I thought I heard you say, you marry him, you say, oh, shit, you heard that. Damn. Oh my god.
He said and you're not going to stay in my dog's bed. You're staying in my bed
The dog has to leave the room when we're intimate, but the dog can sleep on the bed
Right you're here the story. He doesn't make stroke off his INX
I don't know him, but I know who he is.
You know the great story ones.
He said, you know, here's how he talks.
Oh, okay, what?
I had this, I was effing this B, right, in his bed.
And all of a sudden he feels like a licking in his backside.
And he turns and the dog was on the bed licking him.
And he threw the dog off the bed.
And then the girl was like,
Let him in. He just wants to play too. That's why. Oh, no. Are you serious?
No
Oh, then they were playing they're like look at psyche's platforming sicko. I didn't know he was gonna tell that story, but
It was real it really happened or was he just making it up was completely honest that it happened
He had it. Oh my God him job for his girlfriend's dog and then she was like keep letting him do it
He's like no the dog has to leave the room. Yeah, we're gonna say pigs hurt didn't have him, but I don't even want to see those pictures
Wow Mike stroke up you need to tell us that story I do I want to make an erotics erotic story book about all I mean
It's gonna be totally wrong
What is his brother's name because he's been stalking crystal nub or whatever that's his brother
Eric Strokov and Eric, yeah, and Eric, I mean, they both look like they're like, you know, Richard Strokov, not Richard Strokov, Dick Strokov. No, no, no, it's like, it's not like they look like they're basically the bums from like Hollywood or like these, you know, they had these huge beers, they look like like 1970s serial killer.
Both of them. Yep. But no, he shaved his, he looks actually good looking. He shaved all of that. Is he growing it back again?
I don't know but you know he says oh psyche's dirty. I mean he this guy looks like you know
They'd look it with all that beard and hair. Yes
This is a thing. It's like I called dirty by them. I mean I don't know it's like I'm done
I mean it's like I have like
Basically bums calling me a bum. Yeah, and they're streaming what happened to their RV streaming
They they lost the RV what's going on because they're always at their mom's house streaming from there
Yeah, I mean it's like oh the last thing I remember is like they're all getting in the car like a family
They're like we're going to the social services office to go apply for food stamps and they're like we're gonna have some pasta tonight
We're gonna get some wine and so yeah this guy um, I guess bake lips posted. Oh, here's the stroke offs going to
Get their free food. They're like we need to get our free food. But yeah, I mean nothing against it
It's just funny. It's like so many people are afraid to say if they're on public assistance
But they're like, you know proud to go to the office on on the camera and stuff
So, I mean, I just think it was kind of funny. I know they're interesting
But you know again, it's like it's so hard. I try to platform or like anybody that comes
I try to like as long as I'm breaking TOS and stuff
But and it's like but everyone has a problem of me doing that
But then everyone else is like so proud. I let it work. I can talk to everyone
I let it work on Tommy James blah blah
But then it's like I have anybody on my show and it's like oh you're sick
You know you're you're you're affiliated with them
I mean it's like I can talk to people and I agree with them, right?
We don't have to I mean that's the thing we don't have to agree with everybody
We don't have to I mean I say and when we're on actually like this is like a phone call
So no one's gonna reach out on the phone
I wish I say it could reach out and touch me over the phone or this line
I wish and the ghost
I wish, but it's not there yet.
So it's like, you can't, like no one's gonna hurt anybody
on the phone, you know, it's like, it's so.
That's why I-
Yeah, I'm gonna get shit on for being in here tomorrow,
whenever I fucking go on, I don't know.
Maybe not clumsy stream, but if I pop on another stream.
This is such bullshit though shut the fuck up people can have fucking relationships with other fucking people and no
I mean, I would know I never would tell somebody go to this channel go to this but here's the happening yesterday
And then Paige was like you know, she's like oh, I don't like the topic here
So I'm gonna I'm leaving and then she started her own life. Well page. There's page doing I think she's good
But I went over there and I was like hi page and then I was like I was like hey, I was like kind of like
I was like the first show that Paige came and kind of came on in this community and everything and then someone's like
Oh, he's you know, oh stop taking credit for page page of pages and like you pages and no you and then I was like page
Do you remember like coming on a year ago and she's like, well, yeah
And you know what? Yeah, you're that's great and she's like, but yeah, be that pretty much introduced me to everybody and you know
and you know
So I mean she's kind of downplayed it
and then I always give you credit for the record. Thank you. I started with Psyche.
But then Vita turned on her, but Vita blocked Page and said something terrible about her. I mean
in a second, so does anybody know that story? That's what she does and she cries when somebody
says terrible things about her and she'll reach out to everybody to help.
You know, it does attack that person. Yeah, if I talk about somebody or something I already said, but yeah, beauty gets crazy
She does that's why she's happy with her channel because that's what she was looking for before
She was always trying to use everybody to cut to battle her people that hurt her. I mean and now
I don't know. She's a different person when she's live because at first she started doing lives and it was like
What are the games or whatever that they were doing?
drama and
bashing people and
Lies and and you know, just it's ridiculous our old stuff. Yeah, it gets crazy
Good times good times got a hold of like, you know, he added page on Instagram and but then he's like the way he tells the story is a little bit
like well then I saw her legal last name on Instagram and so then I joined her on Facebook because
I wanted her to see my nature photos and stuff like that and it's like but now it's now it's
turned into like oh he's stalking her across social media I mean he just says to say oh I was
recommended in faith I don't know he makes it sound weirder than it was it's okay I mean there are
guys like you know J1 and stuff like that he'll go around and like you know Mason I guess the
drummer kind of does it they go and they they'll a friend every single woman and then they'll start
It says, Psyche said page info to Gramps.
I didn't say anything to anybody.
What did you talk about, BG, your line?
I didn't say, he said he Googled her.
Oh yeah, Psyche said pages info to Gramps.
I did not call her a lesbian golfer.
I don't understand what's going
on. He's not a lesbian
golfer. I am. I'm a gay golfer,
baby. Oh, I'm sorry. My cat's over here knocking stuff down.
Hey, have you heard of the ball washer on the golf course?
That's what I want to do. I want to be a ball washer at the golf course.
You know, I
It seems fitting it seems big
She catches out of it, that's pretty cool
Do you what would have gone actually dinosaur eggs and they all hatched avenge W
Hey, I say it so how have you been though? I mean is like, you know, what's how's the how's the romance? Did you find that Queen yet?
No, I'm breaking up with my
I've been seeing my extra last four months and I'm breaking up with her.
Does she know?
No.
Okay.
Well, here's, I got a card for you.
This one says innocence.
Okay.
So it's like, I think you're innocent in the situation.
I think that you, I don't think you did anything wrong, but I think like, right?
I think that there's innocence somewhere in there for you.
It's like, you know, you tried, you've been in a good try too.
I said, like you tried really hard to do it.
And then it's like, but then there's prosperity coming for you too.
it's like I don't know if she's holding you back from this or distracting or something like that
but there's some kind of um prosperity that will that will result from actually your innocent heart
and you know doing the right thing for yourself and what else do we have I have uh belonging
there's belonging to so it's like you also like I think you're gonna find that you know community
of people they remember you have in it's like where you actually you feel like uh you fit in
Never trust psyche. I never said anything about page two good times ever. All I did was I got the story about it already frightened her
I ain't give any information down or anything
So BG you're just a liar, and you know what you're probably that fat so person like you're probably like that your mom or something like that
That person's I don't know if you know that who that is
So I know person is actually the name of a goatia demon. So that's actually like a person demon
P-U-R-S-O-M, look it up, Gawesha, yeah, anyway.
Ghost, are you there?
Ghost is ghosting us.
Yeah, he's there, maybe he's in the chat?
Yeah, Isaiah, were you a wrestler, Isaiah?
No.
You never wrestled?
No, I did rugby and football.
Oh, okay.
Oh, okay, no wonder.
Yeah, well rugby's pretty hot like I like when all the guys go into that like that circle in touch of those
I chose butts and stuff the scrum. Yeah
You like that Karen
And rugby when they're all like, you know in a circle like hug you know, yeah, that's what that's like in the UK
Yeah
I say in other countries. They don't they don't have much of that here in the state. So I've never seen rugby
Do you still have your uniform Isaiah? No, no, no, we if I sent you a rope uniform
Take a picture of yourself in it and then send me the uniform back on wash
I don't know okay. I don't really care. I mean why not? I don't really care. I said a couple bucks. Yeah shit
I'll go shit. Okay. Hey, you're my phone number. So right?
Probably I think so. Okay. I'll put it backstage and
Hey
And I'll never I'll never hit on you again. I will never mention anything and
If you hit on me, so I keep doesn't matter
And you can give me another day
God, I love look look you fucking I started with you. You can
Thank you. You can't do whatever, but well, I've already popped your streamer streaming cherry in a certain way, right?
Or is that what you say?
Only fucking three years
What that was a year now
Way more than that. Yeah, I remember yeah, I remember like this go two years ago. Yeah
It's almost two years. I mean the time fly I remember remember when I got the manicure on the air and stuff
And you were there too, and I got that manicure everyone that says my see I say has been through my dirty nails
He's been through my clean nails. I mean he's been through every phase of the show. I mean so he knows
But he knows I'm not a bad guy. I'm not a bad guy. I've got my phone in the back stage if you want, but you don't have to worry about it. I'd love you to come.
Um, yeah, gays, actually gays have a lot of loyalty. I am a very loyal person, and I just am not.
Shoot it. Not the lesbians.
Yeah. Well, do you know what a lesbian brings to their second date, um, INX?
Huh?
You know what a lesbian brings to the second date?
Oh, God.
No, I don't know. I don't I'm I don't know lesbians
You know, they move really fast
In relationships. Yeah, the second date is like they're ready to move in and sort of I remember like college went one hit on me
And she was beautiful. I didn't even know she was gay, you know until my
friend Steve told me that that's why she he brought her over I mean but she could have anybody but
she was dating guys and girls and yeah I didn't know she had a crush on me I felt uncomfortable
but you know we became friends and she respected that I don't go that way what was Steve up to
Steve was trying to get a little a threesome action going or something yeah yeah he was
He brought over a girl that he was hope you'd be attracted to was he hope you I think he was hoping for
Something to happen that night. Maybe I don't know
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I went too far. Are you there anybody there ghost? I'm here and I agreed with you
Yeah, I'm not no, I don't know who that is
I and I was just kind of making a joke
But that's like I know a man's guys minds work sometimes and there
So he's like he brought her over to see if how you would
React to or he's definitely wanting to get a show I think so
Or at least watch, you know, but no, no, but you're not like that
But you actually you're but you're really cool though. Yeah, you're very you're very like
You've been very open-minded with me and everything because I know it's like different culture with you like about
The gaze and stuff like that, but it's like, you know, you've never been home a full book or anything towards me
I just know it's like not something you're used to and so it's like basically I was like that too
I was like that too, you know, I think my my brother too is
who were against it completely until I met some in college and I became friends with them and the
first time I was at a party and there was this gorgeous guy that kind of looked like Tom Cruise
but he was vanished and gorgeous guy and he seemed kind of feminine but he wanted to hook up but
but he was still gay he would hook up he was hooked up with girls too but he was mostly in the guys
And the first time I met him, I felt uncomfortable
I'm going through somebody else's yearbook that they had because I felt uncomfortable and
He sat next to me and he goes are you uncomfortable with me because I'm gay and that was the gate first gay person I ever met
Wasn't comfortable and I realized they're humans just like us, but he was gorgeous
He was gorgeous and it's like he preferred guys, but he messed around with girls and I wasn't gonna mess around with him
But yeah, he was he was a beautiful guy. I mean, yeah
I mean, there's a lot of like um, there's a lot of like, you know, I think some women are
attracted to that idea and
Like that and then some women are kind of the turnoff kind of thing, right? But it's like
Even I think that was it. Yeah
Like Hercules in the story like Hercules ended up getting kind of like cupped by his wife
like she would like she he would like he went crazy eventually, but
She's he started dressing in like out like dresses and stuff like that. Like he was wearing dragon stuff Hercules. I mean
masculine man
Can you know if the woman talks him into it? You don't know. Yeah, exactly, right? It's like
Don't know you ever see I'm American pie, too
Like we're that's kind of like I remember watching that we're watching that movie
And it's like there's a scene where they're on this webcam with this hot European girl
And that their European girls are like oh kiss guys and so the guys start kiss and after that happened
All the guys are going gay after that over in the window. They fell in the window. Yeah, they fell in the window
Yeah, did you ever see that movie Karen or in X? No, what was it called?
What I didn't hear American pie to
No, I saw American Pie the first one. I never saw the second part. The second one was more like a they're in college or something
It's like yeah, but they're in college. I never know. No, they're on spring break there
It's the so American Pie 2 is the after-between
graduation and
Right love the American Pie movies. I'm sorry
I mean I was in high school. I was actually like I did here in high school when we watched that
So funny, but it's like nowadays
Guys, you said, oh, Birdie Joyce says, I was not on a webcam.
They were painting, oh, they were painting the house
and they came in their second story window.
That's right.
OK, I remember some webcams up to that movie,
but it must be a different scene or something I'm thinking of.
So we'll kiss, but then you have to kiss each other.
Yeah.
So that's how you do it. I mean, that's how the guys if you're if you want to like make out with a straight guy
Pretty much get a hot. Hey, we have oh, we have a we have another guest. I'm gonna get in there. Hey another hot guy coming in
What do you drink Ken 300 water. Oh, you are
You hung over yeah
You look good, you look good, look at these hot guys on the show.
You can prevent a hangover by continuing drinking into the next day until the end of the weekend.
I'll start drinking later.
What are you drinking? I say you're drinking water too. No, I'm drinking course light. I mean, it's
effectively water kind of at this point, but I drink Fuji water. I'm now drinking, making myself
drink three liters because I don't want to get sick again. Oh, and that was the thing that I get
real dehydrated. I wasn't having enough water because they drew blood from me and it'll get
Oh, she so I got they were able to draw blood this last time no marks or anything
But for the last two years I saw big bruises and now I know that's what it is at that one time
They couldn't draw blood. They tried different
People trying to take blood for me, and I'm thinking where's your supervisor? Maybe she can do a better job
You know and then then I found out through the doctor that it is because I
Um, my body is dehydrates and I never did that before until last year when you're dehydrated. I think it's harder to find the vein or something like that. Yeah, no, they found the vein, but it's that my veins are thin and they couldn't draw blood because not enough water in my body and it made me sick and I get dizzy.
So I'm making myself drink water because I forget.
and i do four mile walks every day and that's another thing it's like i need to drink water
because i i feel dizzy when i don't oh no shit a couple times yeah especially with the heat and
humidity here and i'm like uh i can't stand what i'm not going to drink anymore i'm tired i'm
and it gets hot and all of a sudden everything went white, like I was getting heat stroke,
it's like the doctor gets mad and you gotta keep up with the water, Karen. Just drink a lot,
you need to, you don't need to get sick again.
Yeah, you don't want to get sick, but you've been taking really good care of your health. It seems that just like you know
I am yes, because you know when I got big I was getting
Diabetes to I had high blood pressure and I've never had that before because I've always been athletic all my life
And I let myself go after my mom died. I didn't care it got to the point that I
Couldn't even walk a block at that time. I mean it was now I can walk for a
you know four miles and stuff but yeah it was bad and then and then I lost it
then and then I just lost a little too much when I got sick
Sorry to hear about now now they kind of make fun of that like you're skinny, you know, you know, it's like shit
Just leave me alone. It's I think I'm doing the best I can I'm alive, right?
But you're for skinny
That I was skinny when I was a kid my parents always said I was too skinny, but when I look at the pictures
I was normal. I wasn't skinny. I was always athletic
Yeah
And you still are you still you mean you still are I mean to walk four miles a day. Yeah, I do
I'm active now I go swimming and it's been sucked to this whole week that we have bipolar weather
It's supposed to be sunny and then it rains and then they said it's gonna rain and it's not raining and
Today was supposed to be sunny
So I was ready to go to the pool and now they got the pool closed and
And it's cloudy and it rained a little bit not much, but you know it sucks
Well, we should have a pool party. I wanna meet up. We should have a speedo party and everyone's gonna wear a speedo
I haven't run a speedo since I was fucking like eight years old. It's not happening again.
What kind do you want, Al?
I used to wear the speedo suits. I was in the swim team that my dad forced us to, John. I hated doing the swimming things and stuff.
My lifeguard knows on swim team until I was 15.
Junior lifeguards.
You have to do training, you know, you just have to like swim, I guess, like four Olympic pool lengths in like a minute and 50 seconds or something like that.
And so, in order to get your speed up, you have to wear speedos, so you swim faster, there's less resistance.
Yeah, and you know, our next door neighbor, when we lived in Albuquerque, their daughter was my age, and I remember she'd always be swimming laps because she was training for the Olympics.
And when my cousin came to visit from England, she would.
uh make fun of her not to her face but say look at her she's got muscles built like a guy
and called her a man woman just because she was a swimmer and she went to the olympics you know
she she didn't win though but i remember the pool was made for for laps swimming it didn't have
the deep end like our pool had or diving board it was just a pool made for her because she was
seriously training for the olympics
That's crazy. I mean it's like I do have a good
I guess I have a what are I? Summers build or a scarecrow build. I'm not sure. I want to see
It's a great Summers build, you know, just need a little more muscle. You're good. I need Michael Phelps
I need to take the Phelps. Can you move out here? I say I need a full-time trainer living with me
The dog join the gym you they'll trade they don't have trainers there
Everybody wants Isaiah to do stuff. Isaiah doesn't want to do stuff anymore
No, I want to train myself
Karen I mean look what I've done like you have a ghost here if I say I mean it's like look at all these hot guys
Yeah, yeah, I like ghosts. He said an amazing guy. I'm glad you know what he said everything makes sense
He's a good guy. He is a good guy. Ghost there? Ghost has been talking so much right now. It's crazy. It's fucking wild
Tyler, I'm going to put his picture on the screen, maybe it will cost something.
Let's see the picture of ghosts. I mean good. He's a great-looking guy
I mean they stick very well the people they don't get whether they're bad bad or a good looking no
Nobody likes to have their pictures out there cuz you got crazy trolls that use it and make memes out of it
Or you know, he's gonna say nobody cares what anybody looks like nobody
What he looks like he's a gorgeous guy
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What? That's
not ghost. Okay, that's not
ghost. It isn't good. That it
wasn't good. No, it's not. But
you know people are going to
troll and say, wow, this is ghost
picture. No, but because one of
the last laugh, it actually goes
is a really hot guy. Um, what
is this picture? I mean, a
That's me and Mimi. Oh, I like that. That's a cute two picture
Okay, Jessica a black Jessica rabbit a little bit
The length of hair, that's what mine's like mine's always it's down to the shoulders, you know, but it's so wavy. I hate it
I just want it straight
What is this at this weird? Oh my god, I think we're unusual pictures. Let me see what where's the ghost picture?
I mean, oh the real ghost picture
Crystal Marie I've done as a new old news article of Crystal Marie
There's what yeah, so my awarded world record as youngest youngest inventor of a rock. Yeah
I like that. She's in the Guinness Book of World Records for
Inventing the Rocket. She said, the feminist inventor of a rocket. So, I found the article.
That's so cute. Yep. So, she's telling the truth. I mean, I didn't quite believe it, but
you never know. You never know. Yeah. What else do I have? I mean, I mean.
She's so funny though. You know, I kind of like her except for when she gets mad and goes off.
But yeah, she is funny. She is. Oh, here's Ghost.
Let's see. Let's see how cute he is.
Close. Yeah, it goes. Yeah,
come on. Don't don't knock everything over, Missy. Come on.
I know. Come on. Yeah. You're knocking stuff over. Have you ever seen?
Have you ever seen the movie Ghostbusters? Yes, I did. I think the second one too.
That was a long time ago. Shoot. I don't want my ghost. But oh, here it is. This is called the Stay Puffed Marshmallow Amanda.
Yeah, who is that? I mean, you've shown that a few times. That's Amanda Erickson. That's a real person? Yeah
Yeah, I didn't know that
They love marshmallow man, but basically her faith. That's her face. Yeah
Well, she always she calls me it she calls me like literally she's humanized in her eyes
And so she calls me it I can call her you know a marshmallow Amanda
Anyway, what am I Amanda? Yeah, is that her screen name Amanda? I don't know. Yeah
Oh, that's her avatar. Okay, but that's not her real picture though, right her face. That's her face. Yeah. Oh, that is
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, she used to be in the military, I guess and looks on a military base and stuff
I don't know, but she doesn't like me anymore. She used to be in my mod
Sucks cuz everything you're putting up right all the pictures none of them translate over to stream yard
I'm in the app. No, I don't see any of the pictures you're putting up. I'm on the app and I see them
It's weird. I don't know
No, I have an Android
With the 27 ultra that I got the 26 ultra last August when it just came out they're coming out so fast
So I'm gonna get that phone, but I just got
I've only had this a few months. I think I'm so tired of the new fucking phones dropping each year number one
Because all they do is upgrade the fucking camera and now it's just incremental because I mean shit the cameras are so fucking good
It's just all AI integration now. We're gonna be the next fucking upgrades and it's not just gonna be AI for each new fucking phone
Oh, blah blah blah. Yeah, right? It's gonna. Everything's going AI but to Apple
Shit for Streamyard, right? So anytime anybody
Some people both a lot of people had the issue when people would come in
Hard doing like I mean shit. It was doing it with the app
New people in the panel and I'd lose fucking audio or well, I would
Most people were losing when new people joined in.
Every time anybody left, I constantly lost audio.
Like earlier, when Psyche left the panel for a second,
when it was me easy and ghost.
I had to kick back and rejoin cuz lost fucking audio as soon as like you fucking left the panel
And then I switched to the app and the apps a little better, but then obviously now I can't see fucking cool pictures
I see it
Just like I feel left out
But I just just sucks with the Apple man
I don't understand why to like why yeah, I mean and my sister always had an apple
But they say that's kind of hard to use if you're new to it
It's the
I like Apple because it is the lazy person's smartphone.
Samsung is so much more intricate compared to an Android.
Oh really? I always thought iPhone was.
Because it's hard for them to put apps or when
I worked for AT&T years ago when I was going to college.
I worked there and I remembered people with the iPhones.
No, it was later.
It was something about the iPhone that there were some things they couldn't do, put on there like you can on Android.
Well, there is a lot of shit like Android's got like a way more open.
Like there's a lot more apps for Android.
So it's not available for Apple.
Just, you know, or unless you do some crazy side loading shit, which you fuck all that, we're not going to get into that.
Apple, it's just so simplified and like connected to everything.
One, like, anything Apple-based, right?
Well, okay, yeah.
Yeah, absolutely.
I would recommend it.
If I had mini, there's no settings.
There's no settings for a lot of shit.
And if you guys are into AI at all, like, I'd say, like,
isn't it true, like, if you do, like, a back,
if you get a back mini or something like that,
and just put, like, a robot on it,
that in case for itself, within, like, two years,
with all the free AI, you'll get,
They'll pay for its help in a few years, basically.
You can do a lot of shit with AI and I'll pay off like tenfold for now, but it sucks.
You know, GROC, GROC is actually an agent AI that was like, that had actually made you
own the stock market, say for $200 a month, you can have their like, they'll like,
do stock investing for you and stuff.
People make so much money for $200 a month.
I think they just like, so it's like, they say dream period right now.
If people can figure out what, there's also a lot of free credits and stuff like that.
You can get guys, there's free credits, there's free, there's free API.
There's a lot of ways you can utilize AI to work for you.
Yes.
My baby.
At the same point, it's all going to come back.
Yep.
It's all going to come back.
So make the money now with AI.
Yes, I agree.
But I won't fucking touch your shit because...
Look at it.
Oh my God.
And you're ghost snoring.
Fucking hate AI.
You're ghost snoring?
Yeah.
That's where he is.
He's there snoring on the grill.
He's boring. It's boring. I think he falls asleep on the toilet and starts to snore. Thank you fucking
Shit
I'm bored. I bought a little amount of man. You can hear is you can hear like the acoustics of the bowl when he snores
My god
You can't fall asleep on the panel like that. I can't do that. No, I gotta be as bad when I sleep
I'll never fall asleep on the phone or
I don't mind or anything. Whatever I'm doing, I got to stop and head to the bed and sleep.
He's in the toilet.
In the toilet? So he can fall asleep on the toilet.
In the toilet. That's why you hear the acoustic.
Damn, because there's no way I'd be falling down in the bathroom or something.
Yeah, right. Like I'd pass out.
Yeah, how are you going to sit on the toilet and fall asleep?
Hi, baby.
No, he's like, I mean, ghost is so big.
He's all done to that motherfucker.
Yeah, he did.
He's my baby.
My baby.
You're feeling better?
Aw.
He scared me.
You scared me the other day.
That's not on my toilet.
It's like, all right, if I lean the right way, it's the wall
right on the right-hand side.
If I lean to my left, I'm going to fall straight in the fucking
top shower.
I thought it was like Remington growling.
I was like, what was that?
No, he doesn't growl. He doesn't growl. He just barks like very aggressively.
Thank you. I was crying earlier because of my stupid roommate. Oh, I'm sorry, Rose. I hope your
roommate does better. Rose, I know.
I don't, I think Rose says she's like eating women now, but
I'm glad you're better, baby.
I'm scared, baby.
I say it's going to be sick.
I don't sweep them up.
I'm still technically sick.
So technically we're not together.
I'm just breaking off the link.
When can you and I be official?
Oh, well.
When does hell freeze over
Hell Michigan exists and it freezes over every year, but
Then you're gonna be what's his name good times neighbor, I'm gonna be good times neighbor
I'm gonna be I'm gonna be I say his power bottom
Oh, you're in Michigan. Is that what you said? No, I'm in Ohio. Oh, you're in Ohio right next door
Same shit different colors
Do you like guys that snore I and X can you imagine ghosts on your couch snoring like this or your baby? I know right?
I'm not a snore. Yeah
Earplugs
Wouldn't that wake someone up themselves up if they snore like that? I couldn't go to sleep with snoring it
Maybe wake me up. I can hear my dad from I'd be upstairs. I could hear him snoring
Hey, my mom I go down like he'd be a snoring
You just have his like eyes covered with his blanket. You have his nose in his mouth
And you go, prrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
There used to be a guy that would usually tell them that because women will just block out the sounds
They're gonna get it like I've done that before a block take it out. It's easier
Yeah, I hate it when it goes off sometimes like when you're cooking or you know
Yeah, but that says turn off your phone up
It's like, you know, like I know I know Mason calls me all the time
Mason doing what's going on there? He seems to have a crush on you
Yeah, I mean, I don't know what happened.
I know I'm a very attractive person.
I don't know, but it's like, I want,
I say to fall in love with me.
And what do I get?
Gates and both of us.
I say, you know, you know.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you,
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
Yeah, well, I don't know it goes to the sleep. I don't know. Yeah, I don't want to burn us asleep
I think I'm gonna wrap up, but yeah
INX we've had we have ran on the show yet goes we had Elzo
And every other guest stand down with the show
It was a brief salmon still pissed off. He never lets go of his anger. That's sad. You know, I guess he grew up like that
well
Samman needs, Samman needs to do what I say, get naked in a sauna and get a massage or something like that.
Both of you.
And I can do the massage.
Samman needs a massage.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey guys, what was nice?
And Ghost went to sleep.
He told me to come back up and he's up to sleep.
Yeah.
I say it.
Call me, call me bro.
Oh, we'll do bro. We'll do
Guys have a good day. All right. Bye-bye
Love you